‎该死
Ugh… God damn it.
‎NETFLIX 出品
♪ Inside the room Dr. Doom, prepare for the boom, bam! ♪
♪ I slam ♪
♪ Scream like Tarzan ♪
♪ I be tossin' and flossin' My style is awesome ♪
♪ I'm causing more family feuds Than Richard Dawson ♪
♪ And the survey said, you're dead ♪
♪ Fatal Flying Guillotine Chops off your fucking head ♪
♪ Mister, who is that? Ayo, the Wu is back ♪
♪ Making go Bo! Bo! Like I'm Super Cat ♪
♪ Oh, no, here come The Wu-Tang shogun ♪
♪ Killer to my eardrum Put the needle to the groove ♪
♪ I gets rude and I'm forced To fuck it up, my style ♪
♪ More Afro than Rollo Coming to a fork in the road ♪
♪ Which way to go, just follow… ♪
‎（啊…可恶）
‎太棒了！
This is nuts! This is so crazy!
‎我有啤酒和无糖气泡水
‎我有一瓶烈苹果酒和一包叉骨脆
I've got a hard cider and a bag of Crossbone Crunch.
‎开派对庆祝了
It's a party.
‎我太为你激动了 凯特
I'm I'm just so, so thrilled for you, Kate.
‎敬迪比亚斯基彗星 对吧？
To Comet Dibiasky, right?
‎-干杯！ ‎-好
Cheers!
‎从你发现它的位置来看
It's gotta be, look… It's gotta be an Oort cloud comet
‎一定是来自奥尔特云的彗星
just based on where you saw it.
‎它上次距离太阳这么近
Probably the last time it was this close to the Sun
‎可能远在人类文明之前
was long before human civilization.
‎看它的弧线 天啊 太神奇了
Look at the arc on that thing. God, it's amazing.
‎明迪教授 我们该如何计算 ‎这颗彗星的速度和轨道呢？
How would we find out the comet's velocity in orbit, Professor Mindy?
‎问得好
That is a good question.
‎肯定会很有趣的 我研究生毕业后 ‎就没算过轨道动力学的题了
This will be fun. I haven't done orbital dynamics since grad school.
‎问题是…
Question is, what…
‎卡尔萨根会怎么做？
What would Carl Sagan do?
‎他会回归第一原理
He would take it back to first principles.
‎站心向量为ρ
The topocentric vector is rho.
‎凯特 初始坐标是多少？
Kate, what are the initial coordinates?
21 Twenty-one.
24 Twenty-four.
‎是不是很有趣 各位？
Thirteen. ‎13 This is fun, huh, guys?
‎-哇 你让我兴奋起来了
‎-67 Sixty-seven. Wow. Now you got me pumped.
‎-明迪博士 ‎-好的
Dr. Mindy. All right…
‎你要计算多少个才能…
How many terms do you have to calibrate…
‎根据马斯登85 这是个很好的近似值
Approximation of coordinates in Marsden, '85.
‎现在有了彗星的轨道 ‎我们来看看星历表
Now that we have the comet's orbit, we will check the ephemeris
‎这样可以算出彗星和地球之间的距离
and that will give us the distance between the comet and planet Earth.
‎星历表的数值为什么越来越小？
Why does the ephemeris keep getting lower and lower?
‎明迪教授？
Professor Mindy?
‎各位 要不我们…
You know what, guys? Let's…
‎我们今晚就到这吧？
Let's call it a night, huh?
‎可是相对位置呢？
But what about the relative position?
‎我没算清楚 今晚不行 各位 抱歉
I can't figure this one out. Not tonight, guys. Sorry.
‎-走吧 我累了 ‎-我也是
Let's hit it, man. I'm beat. Me too.
‎-凯特 太棒了 ‎-祝贺你
Kate, this was amazing. Congratulations.
‎嘿 凯特
Hey, Kate.
‎你留下
You stay.
‎（“我希望像我祖父一样 ‎在睡梦中安详地死去）
‎（而不是惊声尖叫着迈向死亡 ‎就像他的乘客们一样”-杰克汉迪）
‎考尔德博士
Yeah, uh, Dr. Calder,
‎密歇根州立大学的教授 ‎和他的研究生们…
a Michigan State professor and his grad students--
‎我是考尔德博士 ‎我正在会上告诉我的团队
This is Dr. Calder. You pulled me out of a meeting
‎我们失去了80亿资金 ‎而你把我叫出来接电话
where I had to tell my team we lost eight billion in funding.
‎我很抱歉 考尔德博士
I am so sorry, Dr. Calder,
‎但我们刚发现的这颗彗星
but we are seeing some awfully strange orbital numbers
‎轨道数据非常奇怪
on this comet we just found.
‎您已经收到邮件了吧？
They should be in your inbox, right?
‎-是这个吗？ ‎-是这个
Is this it? Yeah. This is it.
‎是的
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Let me get Dr. Oglethorpe on the line.
‎我让奥格尔索普博士接电话 请稍等
Please hold.
‎她让我稍等
Uh… Uh, I'm on hold.
‎她要打给奥格尔索普博士 谁啊？
She's calling a Dr. Oglethorpe. Who is that?
‎天啊 我把免提打开吧
Jesus Christ. I'm gonna put them on speaker.
‎“奥格尔索普博士
"Dr. Oglethorpe,
‎行星防御协调办公室主任”
head of the Planetary Defense Coordination Office. "
‎-真有这种地方？ ‎-我不知道
-Is that a real place? I have no idea.
‎（行星防御协调办公室 ‎是真实存在的机构）
‎（这是他们的标志）
‎我是奥格尔索普博士
This is Dr. Oglethorpe.
‎我是肯尼迪航天中心的乔斯林考尔德
Yes, this is Jocelyn Calder
‎嘿 乔斯林
from Kennedy Space Center. Hey, Jocelyn.
‎是这样 我们通过斯巴鲁望远镜 ‎观测到了一个近地天体
Listen, we got a sighting of an NEO from Subaru telescope.
‎好的 为什么不直接报告给 ‎小行星研究会？
Okay. Uh… Why you just didn't report it to the Minor Planet Center?
‎先生 一位教授 ‎和几位密歇根州立大学的学生
It's a professor and a bunch of Michigan State students
‎发现了一个很大的天体
who identified something big.
‎真的？有多大？
Really? How large?
‎有多大来着？
How big we talking?
‎我们观测到其直径大约五到十公里
We clocked it in around five to ten kilometers wide.
‎直径大约五到十公里
About five to ten kilometers wide.
‎那挺大的
Uh… That's a big boy.
‎这位教授是第一个观测到的人吗？
And, uh, was this professor the one who first made the observations?
‎是的 我是明迪博士
Hi, yes. Uh, Dr. Mindy.
‎不 是博士候选人 ‎凯特迪比亚斯基发现的
And And no, PhD candidate Kate Dibiasky found it.
‎我做了轨道计算
I did the orbital calculations.
‎我研究死亡星系中的微量气体
I, uh… I study trace gasses in dead galaxies.
‎有一阵子没发论文了 ‎你可能没听说过我
I haven't published in a while so you probably haven't heard of me.
‎总之这不重要 抱歉 ‎你的问题是什么来着？
But anyway, that doesn't matter. Sorry. What was your question?
‎它的最新轨道预估如何？
What are the most updated estimates on its trajectory?
‎凯特？
Kate?
‎我算了一整天 一直是同一个结果
I've been running it all day. I keep getting the same result.
‎六个月零14天后直接撞击地球
A direct hit of Earth in six months and 14 days.
‎我的结果也一样
Me too.
‎马修 你的计算结果如何？
Matthew, what are your calculations?
‎（美国国家航空航天局）
‎小行星侦察器程序计算的结果 ‎是六个月零14天
Um, Scout program is saying six months, 14 days.
‎我们还有六个月零14天
We got six months and 14 days.
‎直径大约五到十公里
And it's roughly five to ten kilometers wide.
‎也就是…
Which… Which, uh…
‎那是…
Isn't that…
‎灭绝级事件吧？
an extinction-level event?
‎我们别这么激动
Well, let's not be dramatic here.
‎好
Okay, uh…
‎第一步是出差到华盛顿特区来
First move is to get the school field trip out here to DC.
‎我们都冷静一下
Let's all calm down.
‎我需要第一个发现彗星的人 ‎和负责人一起来
I need the person who first had eyes on the comet
‎什么？
and the person in charge. What?
‎…马上把数据分享给剑桥 ‎加州理工和国际天文学联合会
…share this data immediately with Cambridge, Caltech and IAU.
‎等一下 这是机密信息
Wait a minute. This is classified information.
‎怎么回事？
What's happening?
‎我需要交由总统决定
I serve at the discretion of the president.
‎这是真的吗？
Is this really happening?
‎我们让那名学生和死亡星系教授 ‎马上去西卡姆空军基地
…and the dead galaxy professor to Hickam Air Force base.
‎华盛顿特区 对吧？嘿！凯特
DC, right? Hey! Hey, Kate.
‎这不是真的吧？
This isn't happening, right?
‎凯特 这不是真的 这是…
Kate, this isn't real, right? This is, uh…
‎这是某个平行现实 对不对？
This is just some sort of alternate reality, right?
‎说点什么啊
Say something.
‎我得去磕点药
I gotta go get high.
‎我奉命尽快送你们俩去华盛顿特区 ‎去那儿的飞机只有这架
Word is that I need you both in DC fast. Only plane I got going there is that one.
‎总之 我是明迪博士 这位是…
Anyway, I am Dr. Mindy. This is--
‎-你好！ ‎-快走！
-Hi! Oh. Go, go, go!
‎-我们坐哪儿 凯特？ ‎-我不知道
Where do we sit, Kate? I have no idea.
‎有没有什么常用座位…
Is there any customary seating for…
‎搞什么？这是真的吗？ ‎是该死的玩笑吗？
What the fuck? Is this real? Is this a goddamn joke?
‎该死
Holy shit.
‎这不可能是真的 不
This can't be happening. No.
‎-布伦登 你是说布伦登？ ‎-是的 布伦登
-Brendon. You mean Brendon? Yeah, Brendon.
‎不 他不够低调 ‎这都是政治 泰迪 你懂的
You know, he didn't keep his head down. It's all politics, Teddy. You know that.
‎-你们一定就是兰德尔和凯特 ‎-是的 你好
You must be Randall and Kate.
‎我是奥格尔索普博士 ‎你们可以叫我泰迪
Yes. Yes, hi. I'm Dr. Oglethorpe, but you can call me Teddy.
‎抱歉 你刚说你叫…
I'm sorry. Did you say your name…
‎-我应该叫你“泰迪”？ ‎-泰迪
-I should call you "Teddy"? Teddy.
‎-泰迪 ‎-是的
Teddy. Yeah.
‎对 我们叫他泰迪 ‎他可一点都不像泰迪熊
Yeah, we call him Teddy because he ain't no teddy bear.
‎我是西姆斯将军 代表五角大楼
General Themes. I'm the Pentagon's eyes on, uh,
‎负责跟进事件 无论这究竟是什么事
you know, whatever this turns out to be.
‎总统是出了名的不守时 ‎你们刚经历了漫长的飞行 所以…
The president is famously late, and you've had a long flight, so…
‎密歇根州立斯巴达人队
Michigan State Spartans. Mmm.
‎-那是总统办公室吗？ ‎-是的 总统办公室
-Is that the Oval Office? Yeah, that's the Oval Office, yeah.
‎比照片上看起来小很多
It's a lot smaller than in the photographs.
‎总统应该马上就到了 ‎她已经听了情况简述
The president should be here shortly.
‎对吧 斯科特？
She's already been briefed. Correct, Scott?
‎没错
That is correct.
‎我们真的要告诉美国总统
Are we really about to tell the president of the United States
‎还有六个多月
that we have just over six months
‎人类以及所有物种就要彻底灭绝了？
until humankind, basically every species, is completely extinct?
‎是的 这就是我们要说的事 对
Yeah. That's exactly what we're about to do. Yeah.
‎哦 天啊
Oh, gosh. Oh, gosh.
‎对 我说了执法机关
Yes, I said law enforcement.
‎但我没有…你跟我说过他没问题的
But I didn't want… I mean, you told me that he was clean.
‎-总统女士 我是奥格尔索普博士 ‎-请退后
-Hello, Madam President. Dr. Oglethorpe. Step back, please.
‎他过去40年的人生都名声清白
Hello.
‎总统女士 我是奥格尔索普博士 ‎我相信乔斯林已经告诉您…
Madam President, I'm Dr. Oglethorpe. I believe Jocelyn briefed you to…
‎-嘿 杰森 ‎-干什么？
-Hey, Jason. Yeah? What up, yo?
‎伙计 搞什么？这是正事
Come on, man. What the hell? This is real world.
‎我知道 我们需要五分钟
Yeah. I know. We need five minutes.
‎我们的最高法院 ‎大法官提名人有点问题 谢谢
We have a problem with our Supreme Court nominee. Five minutes. Thank you.
‎祝你生日快乐
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
‎祝你生日快乐 亲爱的帕蒂
♪ Happy birthday, dear Patty… ♪
‎记个留言就好 这种事时有发生
Just take a message, and then, stuff like this happens,
‎我不知道是怎么回事
and I don't know what's going on.
‎我不明白我还要跟你说多少次…
I don't understand how many more times I need to tell you…
‎有很多关于 ‎他们的提名人不合格的信息
Well, there's a bunch of stuff about their nominee not being qualified,
‎但我没看到文章写我们的事
but I don't see any articles about our thing.
‎社交媒体上全都在讲
Social media is just going on and on
‎歌手莱丽比纳和电音切罗分手的事
about that singer Riley Bina and DJ Chello breaking up.
‎太糟糕了
That's just too bad.
‎他们看起来是好小孩
They seem like sweet kids.
‎我不认识他们
Hmm. I don't… I don't know them.
‎这…
Which is…
‎-挺遗憾的 ‎-是啊
-It's a shame though. Yeah.
‎-你认识他们吗 凯特？ ‎-认识
-Do you know them, Kate? Yes.
‎但我现在不在乎了
-But I don't really give a shit right now. Oh.
‎这东西卖可贵了
They charge an arm and a leg for this stuff.
‎一个十美元
-Ten apiece ought to do it. Oh.
‎-嘿 拿瓶水 ‎-谢谢
Grab a water. Thank you.
‎凯特的我也一起付
I've got Kate as well.
‎-很好 ‎-谢谢
-Perfect. Thank you.
‎给你20
-Here's a 20. Oh.
‎给
‎-你有零钱吗？ ‎-没有
-You got change? No.
‎-我可以问问站岗的海军陆战队士兵 ‎-是…
-I mean, I could ask the Marine. Yeah…
‎这是抗焦虑的赞安诺
Uh, it's a Xanax.
‎我只吃四分之一片 不然我会…
-I only take a quarter. Otherwise I get… Ah…
‎-凯特 ‎-谢谢
-Kate. Thank you.
‎吃这么多你可要小心了
You know, you should be careful with that much.
♪This eagle's place is in the sky ♪
‎很抱歉 明天两点前我要到达冲绳
Oh! I'm very sorry. I have to be in Okinawa by two o'clock tomorrow.
‎-什么？ ‎-什么？你认真的吗？
What? What? Are you serious?
‎-这事很重要 ‎-我得去镇压当地原住民
-This is very important. I have to go quell the natives.
‎代我向你女儿问好
Tell your daughter I said hello.
‎他和我们一起进办公室 ‎不是很重要吗？我是说…
Isn't it important that he was in the room with us? I mean, what…
‎我该在哪里付钱？
Where do I pay for these?
‎这是免费的
It's free.
‎真的？
Really?
‎是啊 这里是白宫
Yes, it's the White House.
‎零食是免费的
The snacks are free.
‎什么？
What?
‎那位将军
The general.
‎他找我们要买零食的钱 ‎但零食是免费的
He charged us for the snacks, but they're free.
‎天啊
Oh, gosh.
‎他为什么要这么做？
Why on earth would he do that?
‎嘿 朋友们 看来今晚是聊不成了
Hey, peeps, uh, it's not looking like it's gonna happen tonight,
‎我感到非常遗憾
and I feel horrible.
‎我们会送你们去某家酒店
We're gonna put you up in a hotel somewhere.
‎抱歉 总统知道我们为什么来吗？
Excuse me, does the president know why we're here?
‎你在逗我吧
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
‎-他们知道我们为何而来吧？ ‎-知道 但你也听见他们怎么说了
They must not know why we're here, right?
‎-他们有没有意识到… ‎-为明天做好准备
They know. Uh, but you heard 'em. Do they even realize… Be ready for tomorrow.
‎…我们花了多长时间过来…
…how long it took for us to get…
‎（庄园汽车旅馆）
‎然后他们让我们等了七个多小时
And then they made us wait for over seven hours,
‎根本都不叫我们进去 难以置信
but they never called us in. I couldn't believe it.
‎他们当然不会叫你们进去 ‎凯特 你今天看新闻了吗？
Of course they didn't call you in. Kate, have you watched any news today?
‎没有 我一直忙着我们的…项目
No, I've been pretty wrapped up in our… project.
‎马上打开电视
Turn on your TV right now.
‎奥尔林总统正深陷 ‎前所未有的风波之中
President Orlean is in the middle of an all-time shit storm.
‎韦德康隆警长本就是 ‎一位备受争议的提名人
Sheriff Wade Conlon was already a controversial nominee,
‎他没有法学学位 ‎还曾“先开枪后提问”
with no law degree and a record of "shoot first and ask questions later. "
‎（尸检新闻）
‎你在看吗？
You watching?
‎随着他曾在大学期间当裸模的经历
With his background as a nude life model…
‎-被曝光出来… ‎-嗯 我正在看
Yeah, I'm watching it right now.
‎…白宫完全陷入了危机模式
…the White House is in full crisis mode.
‎听我说 我找到五名当时的学生
And, get this. I found five former students
‎他们愿意公开承认 ‎康隆曾在为他们的绘画课做模特时
who are willing to go on record that Conlon got noticeably aroused
‎明显勃起
when he posed for their drawing class.
‎我不为我的行为感到羞耻
I have no shame in what I did.
‎我应该写“明显勃起”
Now, should I say "noticeably aroused"?
‎还是“膨胀”？
Or "engorged"?
‎因为我并不希望读起来像骗点击的
Because I don't want this to read like clickbait.
‎这可是篇正经的文章
You know, this is a real article.
‎我…凯特 能给我点反应吗？
I just… Kate, can I get something from you, please?
‎抱歉
Sorry.
‎-我今晚不在状态 ‎-我们能聊一下吗？
-Out of sorts tonight. Can we have this conversation?
‎我感觉我们总是在回避整个事情
I feel like we're skirting around this.
‎你对我妈有意见吗？ ‎是因为这个吗？
Do you have an issue with my mom? Is that what this is all about?
‎不能跟我说具体是什么事？
You can't tell me what's going on?
‎规定就是这样 别担心
It's just the protocol. Please, don't worry.
‎马歇尔的法学院入学考试 ‎考了172分 我们正在庆祝
Oh, Marshall got a 172 on his LSATs and we're celebrating.
‎真棒 马歇尔 我为你骄傲
Way to go, Marshall. I'm proud of you, buddy.
‎谢谢爸爸 我想你
-Whoo! Thank you, Dad. Miss you.
‎嘿 埃文感觉如何？新药有用吗？
Hey, how's Evan feeling? Are the new meds working out?
‎已经稳定在四了
-I'm a solid four. Ooh!
‎他已经稳定在四了
He's a solid four.
‎比上个月要好 对吧？
Well, that's better than last month, right?
‎明天开会记得要勇于发言 好吗？
You know, just remember to speak up in the meeting tomorrow. Okay?
‎-我会的 ‎-你总是太沉默
-Yeah. I will. You get so quiet.
‎该认领功劳的时候你就有点…
When it's time to take credit, you kind of…
‎她问你是不是同性恋 ‎并没有说你就是同性恋
She asked you if you were a lesbian. She did not say that you were a lesbian.
‎-那是个问句 ‎-嘿 听着 我…
-It was a question. Hey, look, I'm…
‎我可以七个月后 ‎和你妈一起吃个午饭吗？
Can I sit down with your mom to have lunch in, like, seven months?
‎七个…这就过分具体而且非常遥远了 ‎这是…她是我妈啊
Seven… That's weirdly specific and distant. What is… This is my mom.
‎所以…
So… Oh!
‎我听说有个小行星还是彗星什么的
I heard there's an asteroid or a comet or something
‎正让你们发愁
that you don't like the looks of.
‎说说吧 然后告诉我为什么要跟我说
Tell me about it and then tell me why you're telling me about it.
‎你们有20分钟
You got 20 minutes.
‎-20分钟？ ‎-该你说了 博士
-Twenty minutes? That's you, Doc.
‎就是现在
Go. Now. Go.
‎总统女士
Uh… Madam President.
‎大约36小时前
Uh… Approximately 36 hours ago,
‎这位博士候选人 凯特迪比亚斯基
uh, PhD candidate Kate Dibiasky here discovered
‎发现了一颗非常大的彗星
a very large comet.
‎-对 ‎-真为你高兴
Oh. Yeah. Good for you.
‎这颗彗星直径大约五到十公里
A comet between five to ten kilometers across,
‎我们猜测它来自奥尔特云
that we estimate came from the, uh… from the… from the Oort cloud.
‎哇
Wow.
‎那是太阳系最边缘的部分
Which is the outermost part of the solar system.
‎然后…
And, um…
‎然后用高斯轨道测定法
And using Gauss's method of orbital determination
‎同时考虑0. 04角秒的 ‎平均天体测量误差 我们询问了…
and the average astrometric uncertainty of 0. 04 arcseconds, we then asked--
‎-那是什么玩意儿？ ‎-我觉得好无聊
Whoa! What the hell is… What? I'm so bored.
‎告诉我们到底有什么事就行
Just tell us what it is.
‎-什么？别说什么？ ‎-真的 别说了
-What? Stop what? Seriously, stop.
‎明迪教授想说的是
What Dr. Mindy is trying to say is
‎有一颗彗星正朝地球飞来
there's a comet headed towards Earth,
‎根据美国国家航空航天局电脑的计算
and according to NASA's computers,
‎这个天体将落在智利海岸正西方
that object is gonna hit the Pacific Ocean
‎100公里处的太平洋中
at 62 miles due west off the coast of Chile.
‎然后呢？会引发潮汐波？
Then what happens? Like, a tidal wave?
‎不 结果远比潮汐波有毁灭性
No. It will be far more catastrophic.
‎到时将会有数千米高的海啸席卷全球
There'll be mile-high tsunamis fanning out all across the globe.
‎如果这颗彗星发生撞击 ‎威力将相当于十亿颗广岛原子弹
If this comet makes impact, it will have the power of a billion Hiroshima bombs.
‎将会发生10级或11级地震…
There'll be magnitude 10 or 11 earthquakes--
‎等等 你的呼吸节奏很奇怪 ‎让我感觉不舒服
You're breathing weird. It's, uh, making me uncomfortable.
‎抱歉 我只是在努力解释科学研究
I'm sorry, I'm just trying to articulate the science.
‎我知道 但听起来太压抑了 ‎我努力在听…
I know. But it's so stressful. I'm trying to, like, listen--
‎我觉得你没有理解情况的严重性
I don't think you understand the gravity of the situation.
‎我在尽力阐述…
I'm trying to articulate it the best I can--
‎总统女士 这颗彗星 ‎就是我们所谓的地球杀手
Madam President, this comet is what we call a planet-killer.
‎没错
That is correct.
‎这个结论有多肯定？
So how certain is this?
‎撞击概率是100%
There's 100% certainty of impact.
‎拜托 别说100%
Please, don't say 100%.
‎我们可以称之为潜在重要事件吗？
Can we just call it a potentially significant event?
‎-对 ‎-好
Yeah. Yes.
‎但这不是潜在会发生的事
But it isn't potentially going to happen.
‎它一定会发生的
It is going to happen.
‎没错 准确地说是99. 78%
Exactly. 99. 78% to be exact.
‎很好 那就不是100%
Oh, great. Okay, so it's not 100%.
‎科学家从来都不喜欢说100%
Well, scientists never like to say 100%.
‎就当是70%吧 继续往下说
Call it 70% and let's just move on.
‎但概率根本没有70%那么低
But it's not even close to 70%.
‎你总不能到处和别人说
You cannot go around saying to people
‎他们100%会死吧
that there's 100% chance that they're gonna die.
‎那可太疯狂了
You know? It's just nuts.
‎我们应该找我们的科学家们看看 ‎无意冒犯
We should get some of our scientists on this, you know.
‎但你们这么两个人跟着…
No offense, but you're just two people that walked in here with--
‎奥格尔索普博士
Dr. Oglethorpe.
‎奥夫…奥吉尔维博士 对
Dr. Ov… Ogilvy. Yeah.
‎我在美国国家航空航天局 ‎负责行星防御事务已经15年了
I've been head of planetary defense at NASA for 15 years.
‎而明迪博士是 ‎密歇根州立大学天文学终身教授
And Dr. Mindy is a tenured professor of astronomy at Michigan State,
‎迪比亚斯基小姐是那里的博士候选人
where Miss Dibiasky is a doctoral candidate.
‎-很好 ‎-不好意思
Good. I'm sorry.
‎你刚才说“密歇根州立”？
Did you say Michigan State?
‎没错 他们的天文学系非常出色
Exactly. They have an excellent astronomy department.
‎-是的 ‎-得了吧
Yes. Come on, bro.
‎开什么玩笑？ ‎要看我的大学入学考试成绩吗？
You kidding? You wanna see my fucking SAT scores?
‎好了 我们来说重点吧
Okay, let's bottom line this.
‎这件事需要我付出什么？
What is this gonna cost me?
‎你们的要求是什么？
You know, what's the ask here?
‎政府有现成的计划
There are government plans in place.
‎我们可以通过 ‎美国国家航空航天局采取行动
Um, actions we can take through NASA.
‎可以用装备核武器的无人机
Drones that can be outfitted with nukes
‎尝试改变彗星的运行方向
to deflect and hopefully change the orbit of this comet.
‎我们必须马上行动
We must act now.
‎嘿 好的
Oh, hey. All right, all right, all right.
‎中期选举还有多久？
-When are the midterms?
‎-三周 ‎-三周
Three weeks. Three weeks.
‎如果消息在那之前流出 ‎国会那边我们就输定了
So, if this breaks before then, we lose Congress.
‎然后我们就一点办法也没有了
Then there's nothing we can do about it.
‎政治僵局
It'll be gridlocked.
‎时机…糟透了
-The timing is just… It's atrocious.
‎好吧 目前我觉得我们静观其变
Okay, at this very moment, I say we sit tight and assess.
‎-静观其变 ‎-找其他人一起来评估一下
Sit tight and assess.
‎找些藤校毕业生
Let's get some other people on this. Some Ivy Leaguers.
‎你和我一起审阅一下 ‎航空航天局的计划 好吗？
And you and I will review the NASA plans.
‎非常感谢
-Okay? I'd greatly appreciate that.
‎如果我没理解错的话
Am I to understand correctly that,
‎在今天接收了所有这些信息之后
after all of the information you've received today,
‎你做出的决定是“静观其变”？
the decision you're making is to "sit tight and assess"?
‎-不好意思 她谁啊？ ‎-你他妈谁啊？你不是她儿子吗？
-I'm sorry, who is she? Who the fuck are you? Aren't you her son?
‎我他妈是白宫幕僚长 是龙纹身男孩
I'm the fucking Chief of Staff, Boy with the Dragon Tattoo.
‎不用你操心
So I'm doing fine.
‎我们走吧 真是一场闹剧
We gotta get out of here. This place is a freak show.
‎我觉得迪比亚斯基小姐想说的是
I think what Miss Dibiasky is trying to say
‎静观其变的想法是非常非常危险的…
is that the idea of sitting tight is an extremely, extremely dangerous--
‎谢谢 今天总算有件好事了
Thank you. One good thing happened today.
‎好吧 说个趣事
Okay, funny story.
‎我竞选总统的时候
When I was running for president,
‎竞选活动的第一个月 ‎我不得不偷偷抽烟
I had to sneak cigarettes for the whole first month of the campaign
‎因为我抽烟的照片
because, you know, photographs of me smoking
‎价值多少来着 十万美元一张？
went for, what, a hundred grand a pop?
‎所以我一直藏着 但后来受够了
So, I'm always hiding, but, you know, I just got sick of it.
‎我就说：“随便吧 ‎我想抽的时候就要抽”
And I just said, "You know what, I'm gonna smoke whenever I want to. "
‎你猜怎么着？
Guess what happened?
‎-我的民调支持率上涨了三个点 ‎-他们喜欢她的真实
-I went up three points in the polls. They loved that she kept it real.
‎人们喜欢看有魅力的人抽烟
They love watching a smokeshow smoke.
‎我想不到还有哪位总统 ‎让我希望能在《花花公子》上看到
I can't think of another president that I'd ever wanna see in Playboy.
‎这种“世界末日要来了”的会议 ‎这些年来我们开了多少次
Do you know how many, uh, "the world is ending" meetings
‎你们知道吗？
that we've had over the years?
‎经济崩溃、核泄漏 ‎汽车尾气破坏大气层
Economic collapse, loose nukes, car exhaust killing the atmosphere.
‎-异常的人工智能 ‎-干旱、饥荒、瘟疫…
-Rogue AI. Drought, famine, plague…
‎一切皆有可能
-Uh… Everything.
‎外星人入侵、人口增长 ‎臭氧层空洞…
Alien invasion, population growth, hole in the ozone--
‎杰森 嘿
Jason, hey.
‎-拜托你看看屋子里的气氛吧 ‎-对不起 妈妈
-Read the room for once in your life. Sorry, Mom.
‎问题是 我还有工作要做
Point is, I have a job to do.
‎您能明白这是末日级别的事件吧
You do understand that this is an apocalyptic event.
‎一个巨型天体 ‎正朝着我们的地球飞来 速度高达…
This is a large celestial body heading towards our planet at speeds--
‎我明白 明迪博士
Dr. Mindy, I hear you.
‎我听到你说的话了
I hear you.
‎-你应该为自己感到骄傲 ‎-谢谢
-You should be proud. Thank you.
‎我非常重视它 真心的
I'm taking it very seriously. I'm taking it straight in the heart.
‎您不知道听到您这么说我有多欣慰
I'm so glad to hear that. You have no idea.
‎嘿 各位 我们今天聊的事 ‎显然都是超级机密 对吧？
Hey, gang, obviously everything we talked about in here, super classified, right?
‎-对 ‎-很好
Yeah. Cool.
‎多谢你盛装出席
Thanks for dressing up.
‎我们要就这样把消息泄露给媒体？
You're saying we're just gonna leak it to the press?
‎-这不违法吗？ ‎-是的 我们要泄露出去
-Isn't that illegal? Hell yeah, we're going to leak it.
‎你可能没意识到 ‎白宫刚刚把我们打发走了
In case you didn't notice, the White House just blew us off.
‎我男朋友菲利普说他认识一个记者
My boyfriend, Phillip, says he knows a reporter
‎《纽约先驱报》的 那人会和我们谈
from the New York Herald who will talk to us.
‎-阿杜尔格雷利奥 ‎-很好 他是个重要人物
-Adul Grelio. Good. He's a heavy hitter.
‎我还会悄悄联系更多科学界人士
And I'll reach out to more of the scientific community on the down-low.
‎-我感觉这不是我应该有的行为 ‎-你只要讲故事就好
-I just feel like this isn't what I do. You're just telling a story.
‎讲简单点
Keep it simple.
‎别讲数学
No math.
‎可这全是数学啊
But it's all math.
‎一切都始于连接
It all started with a connection.
‎一个简单的姿势创造了许多东西
A simple gesture that created so much.
‎许多选择
So many choices.
‎有时甚至让人觉得多过了头
Sometimes, it can even feel like too much.
‎直到现在
Until now.
‎向各位介绍巴什来福手机
Introducing BASH LiiF.
‎（要有来福）
‎没有生存压力的人生
Life, without the stress of living.
‎（巴什）
‎在我们介绍 ‎巴什公司创始人兼首席执行官之前
Before we introduce the founder and CEO of BASH,
‎请记住不要直接进行眼神交流
please remember to avoid direct eye contact,
‎不要突然移动 ‎咳嗽或露出反对的表情
sudden movements, coughing or negative facial expressions.
‎现在就让我们欢迎彼得伊舍威尔先生
And now, please welcome Sir Peter Isherwell.
‎（彼得伊舍威尔-创始人）
‎我们爱你 彼得！
We love you, Peter!
‎大家好
Hello, everyone.
‎我这一生做过的所有工作
All of my life's work,
‎动力都来自于我渴望有一位朋友
really, I see has been driven by an inexpressible need for a friend
‎完全懂我、能安抚我的朋友
who would understand and soothe me.
‎多年来的工作 ‎凝结出的成果就是巴什来福
And you know, now all those years of work have come to fruition with BASH LiiF,
‎我们的新款巴什14. 3手机
our new BASH 14. 3, uh, phone
‎完全融入了你的每一种感情和欲望
is fully integrated into your every feeling and desire
‎而你一句话也不用说
without you needing to say one single word.
‎如果我觉得…
If I feel…
‎-悲伤 ‎-害怕
-Sad. Afraid.
‎或是孤独
Or alone.
‎巴什14. 3手机切换到生活设定后
The BASH 14. 3 phone, when set to the life setting,
‎它马上通过血压查到了我的心情
instantly senses my mood through blood pressure…
‎还有心跳…
-Uh, heartbeats and-
‎你的脉搏显示 你很悲伤
Your vitals show that you are sad.
‎这会让你振作起来 彼得
This will cheer you up, Peter.
‎你是我最好的朋友
♪ You are my best friend You are my best friend ♪
‎你是我的挚友 你让我开心 挚友
♪ You make me happy… ♪
‎太棒了
Oh, that's wonderful.
‎那段视频
That video. Um…
‎而且它真的会预约
It also, seriously, uh, schedules
‎附近的专业诊治疗程
a therapy session with a nearby professional,
‎确保忧伤的情绪不会再回来
so we can make sure that these sad feelings never ever ever return.
‎-我可以说句话吗 伊舍威尔先生？ ‎-不可以
-May I say something, Mr. Isherwell? No.
‎为了支持巴什来福手机 ‎我要正式宣布…
And to support, uh, BASH LiiF, uh, I wanna officially announce…
‎手机都给我 这不是你们的
Oh, give me the phones. They're not yours.
‎说再见
Say bye.
‎再见 伊舍威尔先生
Bye, Mr. Isherwell.
‎再见 彼得
Bye, Peter.
‎我爱你 彼得
Um, I love you, Peter.
‎小狗抱公鸡的视频真的能优化
Are you sure the video of the puppy on the rooster
‎幼年感记忆消费群体的表现吗？
is optimizing our prepubescent sense memory consumer sector?
‎我觉得鸟类很吓人
I find the bird quite threatening.
‎我们一定会核对这部分数据
We will cross-check the data on that, for sure.
‎伊舍威尔先生 ‎保罗德班特让我把这个给你
Mr. Isherwell, Paul Debent wanted me to give this to you.
‎他是从一个墨西哥的 ‎天文学家朋友那里拿到的
He got it from an astronomer friend of his in Mexico.
‎天啊
Oh, my.
‎（纽约先驱报）
‎这件事我们还有谁的确认 阿杜尔？
What other confirmation do we have on this, Adul?
‎我和华盛顿的奥格尔索普博士聊过 ‎他确认了这件事和相关计算
I've spoken to Dr. Oglethorpe in DC and he confirmed it and all the math.
‎我还给哥伦比亚大学的 ‎弗兰克斯博士看了
Then I showed it to Dr. Franks at Columbia,
‎他都惊呆了
and he almost fell out of his chair.
‎说实话 我一开始还很怀疑
So, look, I have to admit. I was very skeptical at first,
‎但一切都很可信
but this is all quite credible.
‎计算很可靠
The calculations are credible.
‎天啊
Jesus.
‎总统真的说了要静观？
And the president really said to sit tight?
‎-是的 ‎-“静观其变”
Yes. That's correct. "Sit tight and assess. "
‎她可能在操心中期选举
She's probably worried about the midterms.
‎我们得快速行动
We need to move fast.
‎联邦部门会声称他们违反保密协议
The feds will claim breach of security,
‎给他们两个找一个公益律师
so make sure these two get a pro bono attorney.
‎-你们可以用我的律师 ‎-你现在肯定付得起费用
You can use my attorney. You can certainly afford it now.
‎我们要雇用律师？
We're gonna hire a lawyer?
‎-没这个必要 ‎-我觉得有必要
That wasn't necessary. It was.
‎不好意思
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry.
‎没这个必要
That was not called for.
‎我有个问题
I just have a question here.
‎我们只是告诉人们
How is it criminal if we just tell people,
‎告诉公众我们所看到的东西 ‎告诉他们真相 怎么就成犯罪了？
like the public, you know, what we saw, and tell them the truth?
‎他上节目前要确保让他接受媒体训练
Make sure this one gets media training before he hits the shows.
‎他看起来反应慢了半拍
He seems a step slow.
‎我需要媒体培训是什么意思？
What does that mean, I need media training?
‎他们希望我们 ‎参加《天天揭底》节目
They want us on a show called The Daily Rip
‎要在文章出版前一早就赶过去
first thing in the morning before the article comes out.
‎知道《天天揭底》是什么节目吗？
You guys know what The Daily Rip is?
‎那是最棒的节目 大家都想上
It's like the best show. Everyone wants to be on it.
‎布里和杰克之间的火花太赞了
Brie and Jack have legendary chemistry.
‎他们曾经邀请我去过一次
They asked me to go on once.
‎我兴奋到连续两晚睡不着
I was so excited I couldn't sleep for two nights,
‎但后来因为时长把我剪掉了
but then they cut me for time.
‎现在想起来我依然很难过
Still hurts me to think about that.
‎我知道你说的是哪个节目 ‎我妻子爱看
I know what show you're talking about. My wife loves that show.
‎你能告诉我到底怎么回事吗？
Okay, can you just tell me what this is all about? Okay?
‎你没读我写的关于 ‎康隆在美术课上硬起来的文章
'Cause you haven't read my article on Conlon getting hard in the art class.
‎现在阿杜尔格雷利奥 ‎屈尊来处理你的事
Now Adul Grelio has come down from his mountaintop for your thing.
‎而你一个字都不透露给我？拜托
You won't even give me a lousy pronoun? Come on.
‎一颗比灭绝恐龙的小行星 ‎还要大的彗星
A comet, bigger than the asteroid that destroyed the dinosaurs,
‎正朝地球撞过来
is headed directly at Earth.
‎如果不改变它的运行轨道 ‎整个地球就完了
If it isn't deflected, the entire planet dies.
‎等等 你刚才说什么？
Wait, what did you just say?
‎是游戏里的情节
It's for a video game.
‎你认真的吗？
Are you being serious?
‎是的
Yes.
‎哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
‎哦 我的天！搞什么啊？
Oh, my God! What the fuck, man?
‎我也爱你 好 是的
I love you too. All right. Yeah.
‎两位 我们得往前走了
Hey, guys, we gotta keep walking, all right?
‎走吧
Come on.
‎-是明迪博士和迪比亚斯基小姐吧？ ‎-对
-You must be Dr. Mindy and Miss Dibiasky? Yes.
‎你们能来参加节目 ‎杰克和布里非常高兴
Jack and Brie are so excited to have you on the show.
‎真的吗？他们认识我们？
Really? They know who we are?
‎白宫否认和他们见过面
White House is denying they even met with them.
‎混蛋永远是混蛋
Well, assholes will always be assholes.
‎（《天天揭底》）
‎你们好 我是塔利亚
Hi, I'm Thalia.
‎《先驱报》让我来给你们选服装
The Herald sent me to help with your wardrobe.
‎我不穿这个
Oh, I'm not wearing that.
‎你的脸部结构其实挺棒的
Yeah, you actually have really great facial structure.
‎我把胡子往下剃一点…
How 'bout if we trim this beard down a little bit and--
‎我喜欢你的头发
I love your hair.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎我们要怎么分工？我说一下发现过程
How are we gonna do this? I talk about the discovery and you…
‎你说一下采取行动的紧迫性
talk about how urgent it is that we take action.
‎我们要怎么说？我的意思是…
How do we say it? I mean…
‎-我们应该练习一下 写好稿子吗？ ‎-要喝点水吗？
-Shouldn't we practice it or write it out? Can I get you some water?
‎水 好的 水就可以
Yeah, water. Yeah, water would be nice.
‎你来了
You are here now. You are here now. You are here now.
‎吃葡萄不吐葡萄皮儿
Eleven benevolent elephants. Eleven benevolent elephants.
‎我要吃点赞安诺
-Just gonna take some Xanax. Hmm.
‎有时候我会吃…
I take it sometimes when I…
‎凯特 这次不行
Kate, not this time. Not this time.
‎他需要深呼吸 开口说话 明白吗？
He just needs to breathe and speak up. You know?
‎他可以的 我知道他能做到
He's got this. I know he does.
‎哦 天啊 冷静
Oh, God. Come on.
‎你来了
You are here now. You are here now. You are here now.
‎哦 天啊！
Oh, God!
‎我都说了 别再喝便宜酒了
You gotta stop drinking the cheap shit.
‎-就两杯 ‎-是哦 两杯半
-It's only two glasses. Yeah, two and a half.
‎-倒计时20秒 ‎-总是迟到
We're 20 out. Always running late.
‎确认一下视线
Let's make sure that our eye lines,
‎不要朝向杰克和布里 可以吗？
that we're not looking at Jack and Brie, please, all right?
‎提示就位
And cue the package. Two glasses. Here we go again.
‎-胸部没问题吧？ ‎-是的 要直播了
-Ladies okay? Yes. And we're live.
‎布里 今天我有消息要告诉你 听好
Brie, I've got something for you today. Listen to this.
‎奥尔林总统的最高法院提名人
President Orlean's Supreme Court nominee, Sheriff Conlon,
‎康隆警长被认出曾出演90年代早期
has now been identified as appearing in a softcore porn cable show
‎-隐晦色情电视节目… ‎-真荒唐
-from the early '90s… Ridiculous.
‎…名叫《缎面床单之夜》
-…called Satin Sheet Nights.
‎-此事不断发酵… ‎-哦 我的天
-This story just keeps going and going… Oh, my gosh.
‎那是莱丽比纳吗？
Is that Riley Bina?
‎-是的 那是… ‎-真的？
Yes, well, it's a… Really?
‎她本人要娇小很多 是不是？
She looks a lot smaller in person, doesn't she?
‎上马吧 牛仔
Ride 'em, cowboy.
‎很好
Good. Hee-haw!
‎嘿 各位好 我是节目工作人员肖恩
Hey, everyone. I'm Sean from the show.
‎我们会…杰克和布里 ‎会聊十分钟高院提名人
Uh, we're gonna do… Jack and Brie are gonna do ten on the SCOTUS nominee.
‎-然后莱丽比纳上场… ‎-我可以聊我的单曲 对吧？
-Riley Bina, you'll come on and I get to talk about my single, right?
‎部分盈利会捐给海牛保护区
A portion of the profits goes to the manatee sanctuaries.
‎是的 但要先聊分手
Yes, but the, uh, breakup first.
‎然后是明迪教授和迪比亚斯基小姐
And then Dr. Mindy and Miss Dibiasky,
‎你们上去讲你们发现的行星
you'll come on and talk about that planet you discovered.
‎彗星 我们发现的是彗星
Uh… Comet. We found a comet.
‎他们知道我们是来聊什么的 对吧？
They know what we're here to talk about, right?
‎当然 杰克和布里可喜欢聊科学了
Of course. Jack and Brie love doing science segments.
‎记住 要轻松有趣
Just remember, keep it light, fun.
‎杰克和布里喜欢愉快的氛围
-Jack and Brie love having a good time.
‎这感觉不太妙
That's not promising.
‎你们发现了一颗彗星？真棒
You guys discovered a comet? That's so dope.
‎我背上纹了一颗流星
I have a tattoo of a shooting star on my back.
‎真好
-Oh. That's terrific.
‎我们也听说了你分手的事 ‎我们想说…
We heard about your breakup too, so we just wanna say…
‎我们感到很遗憾 对吗？
We're very sorry, right?
‎真遗憾 你看起来是个…很棒的人
We're real sorry. You seem like a… great person.
‎管好你自己吧 老东西
Why don't you mind your own business, you old fuck?
‎好的
Okay.
‎不骗你 我的朋友们
Not gonna lie, but, um, my friends
‎还有嗡嗡军团都超棒
and my Vroom Vroom Army have been so amazing.
‎我非常感激 但说实话 这很艰难
So, I'm really grateful for that. But, yeah, I can't lie. It's been hard.
‎-你是榜样 非常出色 ‎-是很多人的榜样
-You're an inspiration. It's incredible. To so many.
‎你在认真面对这份痛苦
You're really owning that pain.
‎杰克 我觉得此刻在这里
You know, Jack, I feel like there's some kind of conversation
‎我们应该进行一些对话
that we need to be having here. Is there any message
‎你有什么想对前任电音切罗说的吗？
that you would like to send to your, uh, ex, DJ Chello?
‎这个…
You know, um…
‎如果有什么想说的 我们来…
If there's something--
‎-是的 ‎-对着这边的镜头
-Yeah. Right here in this camera.
‎跟他说 把镜头当成他 ‎把你的想法都告诉他
Tell him. As if that was him. You tell him exactly what you're thinking.
‎好
Okay, um…
‎小切
Chell.
‎我还爱你 在这么多个不眠之夜后
I still love you, and, um, after many sleepless nights,
‎三个
three,
‎我希望你回来
I wanna take you back.
‎不好意思
I'm sorry. Whoa, uh…
‎-可以吗？ ‎-是
-Is that okay? Yeah.
‎-他出轨了 ‎-哦 我的天 你们…
He cheated on you. Oh, my God. You guys…
‎是的
Yeah. I do.
‎消息在嘀嘀平台都炸开了 ‎嗡嗡上也是
-Diddly just exploded. So did Vroom Vroom.
‎巴什新闻刚给我发了八条推送
BASH News just sent me eight push notifications.
‎-关于这事？ ‎-是的 看
-About this? Yeah, look.
‎我的手机刚刚购买了 ‎电音切罗的最新单曲
My phone just purchased DJ Chello's latest single.
‎什么…都没征求我的同意
What the… It just did that without asking.
‎我得知电音切罗 ‎此刻正和我们视频连线
I'm being told that we have DJ Chello live on a Mugg link.
‎-他有什么要为自己说的？ ‎-我爱这里的制作人
-What's he got to say for himself? I love the producers here.
‎嘿 宝宝 嘿
Hey, baby doll. Hey.
‎-嗨 亲爱的 ‎-他流泪了
-Hi. Hi, baby. He's in tears.
‎-你的宝贝犯错了 ‎-我知道
-Your kid messed up bad. I know.
‎巴洛克女士那晚在俱乐部没穿内裤
Lady Baroque wasn't wearing any panties in the club that night.
‎-没关系 ‎-我脑子坏了
-It's fine. I just got all crazy.
‎没办法思考 我犯了错
I wasn't thinking straight. I made a mistake.
‎但我爱的一直是你
But, look, it's always been you.
‎我明白 没关系
Oh! I get it. It's okay.
‎我也和她睡过 ‎就在去年的全球音乐节
I hooked up with her too, last year at the Music Globes
‎在我和掘金队的大前锋私奔之前
right before I ran off with that power forward from the Nuggets,
‎这些都不重要了
and none of that matters.
‎“分手炮已过时 试试分手恋爱” ‎怎么样？
What about "Forget breakup sex. Try breakup relationship"?
‎-很好 ‎-拜托
-That's good. Come on.
‎“十大著名劈腿复合案例” 各位
"Ten famous second chances for two-timers, " guys.
‎这不现成的么
It's on a plate.
‎我一直很害怕 ‎但说实话 现在我不怕了
I've been scared, but, honestly, I'm not scared anymore.
‎好 谢谢
Okay.
‎我的小宝贝 你愿意嫁给我吗？
My little bumblebee, will you marry me?
‎哦 我的天 当然
Oh, my God. Of course. Oh, wow.
‎-小切 当然 ‎-太好了！
-Chell, of course. Yes!
‎-好！ ‎-太好了
-Yes! That's sick.
‎-哦 我的天 ‎-好！
Yes!
‎好了 电音切罗
All right, DJ Chello.
‎怎么回事？ 这…
What is happening?
‎又买了一张
Just bought another.
‎-他们是谁来着？ ‎-他们是最有名的…
-Who are these people again? They're like the biggest names…
‎今天真是值得放烟花庆祝的日子
Well, the fireworks have certainly gone off today.
‎-是的 ‎-多棒啊！
-They have. What a zinger!
‎是的
Yes, they have.
‎我们从求婚转向一些科学实验
From a wedding proposal to a little science experiment.
‎等会儿我需要做头皮按摩 ‎再来杯马提尼
I'll need a temple rub and a martini later on.
‎我们今天最后一组嘉宾 ‎有重大的天文发现
Our last guests today have made a pretty big discovery in space.
‎天文学家兰德尔明迪博士
Astronomer Dr. Randall Mindy
‎和博士候选人凯特迪比亚斯基小姐
and PhD candidate Miss Kate Dibiasky are here.
‎欢迎来到我们的节目
Welcome to the show.
‎在继续谈话前 ‎我可以问个问题吗？我一定要问
Can I ask you one thing before we go any further? I have to know this.
‎太空中存在生命吗？
Is there life out there?
‎能告诉我们吗？有还是没有 请回答
-Can you tell us? Yes or no, final answer.
‎我们没有数据
We don't have the data.
‎但在广袤的太空中 ‎有什么不可能的呢？
But sure, in the vastness of space, why not?
‎对 外星人是真实存在的
Yes, aliens are real.
‎我就知道我会喜欢这个人 ‎我说的吧？你欠我50块
I knew I'd like this guy. Didn't I tell? You owe me 50 bucks.
‎我并不认同飞碟之类物体的存在
I'm not saying there's little green men in flying saucers--
‎-别配合他 明迪博士 ‎-他就是这么说的
-Please don't encourage him, Dr. Mindy. That's what he's saying.
‎这对话没完了
We'll never get out of here.
‎杰克刚才是开玩笑的
Now, Jack was having some fun here.
‎-爸爸看起来很棒 ‎-他们怎么…
-Dad looks great. What did…
‎-挺帅的吧？ ‎-他们给他修了胡子
-Doesn't he look good? They did something with his beard.
‎关于外星人 但…
With the aliens…
‎他真的…确实帅了
Really… He really does.
‎-太多了 ‎-兰德尔博士…
So much. Dr. Randall…
‎-你会后悔的 ‎-你从来都不喜欢他的
You'll regret it. Now, look, Jack's just having some fun here
‎杰克刚刚是在拿外星人之类的开玩笑
with the aliens or whatever,
‎但《纽约先驱报》 ‎刚刚发布了文章 讲述…
but there's a New York Herald story that's just come out that talks about…
‎继续保持 你很棒
Keep it right there. You're doing good.
‎-…你们二位的发现 ‎-是的 布里
-…the two of you have made. That's right, Brie.
‎凯特在用斯巴鲁光学望远镜 ‎观测超新星时…
Kate was, um, observing supernovas…
‎那是你女朋友？
Yo, that's your girl?
‎-是的 ‎-不赖啊
-Yeah. Not bad.
‎…一个令人震惊、十分重大的发现
…an absolutely shocking and once-in-a-lifetime discovery.
‎我都不知道斯巴鲁还造望远镜
I had no idea that Subaru made telescopes.
‎一定很激动人心 告诉我们 ‎你发现了什么 迪比亚斯基小姐
This has to be exciting. Tell us what you found, Miss Diabasky.
‎我当时在监测爆炸恒星
Um, I was monitoring exploding stars
‎以辅助测算宇宙扩张并…
to help measure the expansion of the universe and--
‎-为了你的博士学位 对吗？ ‎-是的
-For your PhD, right? Yeah.
‎我看到了不认识的天体
I saw something I didn't recognize.
‎那是一颗彗星
It was a comet.
‎很大
A big one.
‎径直向地球飞来 很有可能会撞上
It's headed directly at Earth, and it really likely will hit.
‎听起来非常让人激动
This sounds very, very exciting.
‎爆炸恒星 原来星星会爆炸啊
Exploding stars, like, stars actually explode.
‎这个天体有多大？
Um, how big is this thing?
‎会撞毁谁家的房子吗？ ‎有没有这种可能？
Can it destroy someone's house? Is that possible?
‎这颗官方名 ‎将是迪比亚斯基彗星的天体…
Well, Comet Dibiasky, which is what it will officially be named--
‎-以她命名？ ‎-对 她的名字
After her? Yeah, after her.
‎-祝贺 ‎-真荣幸 是啊 祝贺
Congratulations. What an honor. Congratulations.
‎直径大约六到九公里
It's somewhere between six and nine kilometers across.
‎-所以… ‎-好大
-So It's big.
‎它会摧毁整个地球
It would damage the entire planet.
‎不只是一幢房子 明白吗？
Not just a house, you know?
‎整个星球
The entire planet.
‎好吧 它极具破坏性 它会直接撞到
Okay, as it's damaging, will it hit this one house in particular
‎新泽西海岸的某个房子吗？ ‎那是我前妻的家
that's right on the coast of New Jersey? It's my ex-wife's house.
‎可以做到吗？
Can we make that happen?
‎你和雪莉的关系很好的 别闹了
You and Shelly have a great relationship. Stop.
‎别闹了
You need to stop.
‎好 但说句公道话 那房子是我买的
I will, but in all fairness, I actually paid for the house.
‎非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
‎不好意思 是我们没说清楚吗？
I'm sorry, are we not being clear?
‎我们想告诉你们
We're trying to tell you
‎整个星球就要毁灭了
that the entire planet is about to be destroyed.
‎-好的… ‎-这个 就是…
Okay, um… Well, it's, you know…
‎我们就是这样的风格 ‎坏消息也要轻松有趣
It's something we do around here. We just keep the bad news light.
‎是的 有助观众消化信息
Right. It helps the medicine go down.
‎说到消化 明天我们会请到…
Speaking of medicine, tomorrow we've got--
‎也许整个星球的毁灭
Well, maybe the destruction of the entire planet
‎不需要搞笑
isn't supposed to be fun.
‎也许它就应该让人恐惧不安
Maybe it's supposed to be terrifying.
‎不 拜托不要这样
And unsettling. No, please don't do that.
‎-你们应该彻夜难眠… ‎-拜托
-And you should stay up all night… Please.
‎…每晚哭泣
…every night crying,
‎我们所有人都死定了！
when we're all 100% for sure gonna fucking die!
‎嘿 凯特…
Hey, Kate.
‎抱歉
I'm sorry.
‎嘿 伙计
Hey, man.
‎我弟弟有躁郁症 ‎如果你需要和别人倾诉…
My brother has bipolar disorder. So if you ever need anyone to talk…
‎好吧
-Uh… Okay.
‎她一直这样吗？
Is she always like that?
‎-我… ‎-是我说错话了吗？
-I Something I said?
‎是吧？
Right?
‎也许我应该 ‎把多出的那颗赞安诺给她吃的
Maybe I should have given her that extra Xanax that I had.
‎如果你的赞安诺不够的话 ‎我们都有足够的储备给她吃
Listen, if you don't have enough, we all have enough around here for her.
‎一勺赞安诺有助消化 对吧？
A spoonful of Xanax makes the medicine go down, right?
‎没错 很好
That's right. That's good.
‎-我们一定得让你再来 ‎-我就知道我会喜欢他
-We're gonna have to get you back. I knew I'd like this guy.
‎-他是托儿吗？ ‎-我就知道
-Is he a plant? I knew it.
‎好了
Okay.
‎帅气的天文学家
Well, the handsome astronomer
‎随时可以再来 ‎但那位大叫女士就算了
can come back anytime, but the yelling lady, not so much.
‎她就算了 明天和我们一起迎接
Not so much. Join us tomorrow when our guest will be the man
‎很多人说会在两年内 ‎挑战奥尔林总统的那位嘉宾
that many say will challenge President Orlean in two years.
‎也就是参议员杰夫勒纳
Senator Jeff Lerner will be here.
‎另一位嘉宾 ‎是误判杀人犯米歇尔威姆斯
And wrongly-convicted murderer, Michelle Weems,
‎她将讲述在《众星斗舞》 ‎饱受争议夺得第三名的经历
talks to us about her controversial third-place finish on Celebrity Dance Off.
‎-我以为她会夺冠的 ‎-是啊 我依然认为她有罪
-I thought she would've won. Yes. I still think she's guilty.
‎-这里是《天天揭底》 各位 ‎-祝各位愉快
-That's The Daily Rip, guys. Have a great day.
‎-结束！ ‎-节目结束了？
And we're out! The show's over?
‎-我是说 没有… ‎-是的
-I mean, didn't… Yeah.
‎-我们想说的内容讲清楚了吗？ ‎-不 结束了
-Did what we wanted to say come across? No, it's over.
‎你表现很好 但我觉得那个 ‎鲻鱼头女孩需要接受一些媒体培训
You were great, but I think mullet girl, she probably needs some media training.
‎-真的吗？ ‎-是 她糟透了
-Really? Yeah, no, terrible, buddy.
‎谢谢 比利
Oh… Thanks. Thanks, Billy.
‎我们一般会在五点员工会议后 ‎去安德林喝一杯
Uh, we usually get drinks at Aundrine's after our five o'clock staff meeting.
‎挺有意思的 你也来吧
You know, it's fun. You should come.
‎我看看吧 谢谢你邀请我 谢谢
Oh, I'll have to see. Thank you for the invitation. Thank you.
‎凯特？
Kate? Kate?
‎-凯特？ ‎-嘿 你表现特别好
-Hey. You were awesome.
‎谢谢
Oh, thanks.
‎能给你拍张照片 ‎放进我的资料集吗？
Can I get a photo of you for my portfolio?
‎-当然 ‎-谢谢
-Yeah, sure. Thanks. Thank you.
‎可以看到 这个高峰出现在 ‎莱丽比纳要和电音切罗复合的时候
You can see this spike here is when Riley Bina asked to take DJ Chello back
‎在你们前面那一部分
on the segment before you.
‎可以看到所有社交媒体上都有讨论
We saw engagement across all social media platforms.
‎那我们的部分呢？
Hmm. And what about our story?
‎兰德尔和凯特
Randall and Kate,
‎你们的电视露面在迪比亚斯基小姐 ‎骂人时获得了不错的流量
your TV appearance got some nice traffic when Miss Dibiasky cursed.
‎但不幸的是 这马上引起了负面效果
But, unfortunately, there was an immediate backlash
‎成了表情包
-that quickly became a meme.
‎天啊
Oh, Jesus.
‎（疯子-看眼神就知道）
‎-太可怕了 ‎-他们觉得我疯了
-Oh, that's terrible. They just think I'm crazy.
‎看啊 这根本没必要吧
I mean, look at that. That's so unnecessary.
‎-继续吧 艾琳 ‎-好
-You can move on, Erin. Yeah.
‎这太…网上允许这种事情发生吗？
That is just so… Is that even allowed on the Internet or…
‎图应该是处理过的
I think that's Photoshop, Kate.
‎有个小窍门 ‎就是别往心里去 因为…
The trick is to not take it personal…
‎另一方面 ‎明迪博士获得了很高的喜爱度
Dr. Mindy, on the other hand, had some very high favorables.
‎“素食*宝贝”说 ‎“喵！我喜欢星星猛男”
Vegan*Babe wrote, "Meow! Me likey hunky Star Man. "
‎有些账号称他为 ‎“眼神迷离的末日先知”
Uh, some accounts called him "The Bedroom Eyes Doomsday Prophet"
‎或AILF ‎即“我最想睡的天文学家”
or A-I-L-F, which means "astronomer I'd like to fuck. "
‎这完全毫无关联 是不是？
Oh… I don't see what that has to do with anything, do you?
‎以上就是全部内容
And that's everything.
‎（《纽约先驱报》呈现）
‎没有任何网站推送了我们的文章
We did not feature or push on any sites,
‎整体点击 ‎低于普通天气和交通相关文章
and clicks overall were below basic weather and traffic stories.
‎就这样？
So that… That… That's it?
‎-我就知道 ‎-就这样
I knew it. That's it.
‎-谢谢你 艾琳 ‎-不客气
-Thank you, Erin. Yeah, no problem.
‎我不明白
I don't… I don't understand.
‎我不明白 没有任何反应
I don't understand. There's no response.
‎一点都没有…人们为什么不害怕？
There's absolutely no… Why aren't people terrified?
‎我们该怎么说？该怎么做？
What do we have to say? What do we have to do?
‎墨西哥和西班牙 ‎有科学家正在审核数据
There are scientists in Mexico and Spain who are currently going through the data,
‎韩国表示…
and, uh, South Korea has expressed--
‎太好了 韩国
-That's great. South Korea. Hey.
‎我们不要忽悠彼此了
Let us not bullshit each other.
‎总之 你们跟我们说 ‎科学证明它100%真实
The bottom line is, you guys told us the science was 100%.
‎而它不是 现在我们看起来就像傻子
It's not. Now we look like idiots.
‎-不 谁说科学不是100%真实？ ‎-你说什么？
-No. Who said the science is not 100%? Excuse me?
‎我想跟这个人谈谈 你告诉我谁说…
I wanna talk to this person. You tell me who said the science--
‎乔斯林考尔德博士 ‎美国国家航空航天局局长
Dr. Jocelyn Calder, the head of NASA,
‎称之为“接近歇斯底里的表述”
just came out calling it "more near-miss hysteria. "
‎是她让我们不要说出去的
She's the one who told us not to say anything.
‎“接近歇斯底里的表述”
"More near-miss hysteria. "
‎她是天文学家吗？
Is she even an astronomer?
‎她是航空航天局局长 ‎但也许她不知道自己在说什么
She's the head of NASA, but maybe she doesn't know what she's talking about.
‎她是航空航天局局长 但是
She's the head of NASA, but look,
‎她还是“前麻醉师 ‎和奥尔林总统的大额捐助者”
she's a "former anesthesiologist and a President Orlean super donor. "
‎我们别这么激动
Let's not be dramatic here.
‎都是腐败
It's all corrupt.
‎是 但问题是阿杜尔说得对 ‎这个事情还有严肃讨论的空间
Yes, but the point is that Adul's right. There's still serious debate.
‎现在《先驱报》成了那个闹笑话的人
And now the Herald has egg on its face.
‎这个故事我们只能讲到这个地步了
We've taken that story as far as it goes.
‎女士们先生们 祝你们末日愉快
Ladies, gentlemen, I wish you a very pleasant end of times.
‎这不是故事 好吗？
It's not a goddamn story, okay?
‎准确来说我们还有六个月十天
We have precisely six months, ten days,
‎两个小时11分41秒
two hours, 11 minutes and 41 seconds,
‎一颗希克苏鲁伯陨石两倍大的彗星
until a comet twice the size of Chicxulub
‎会撕破我们的大气层 ‎灭绝地球上所有生物
tears through our atmosphere and extincts all life on Earth.
‎你什么时候算的？
When did you do those calculations?
‎我把撞击时刻记在减肥应用里了
I put the moment of impact on a diet app.
‎我的减肥周期结束 撞击就会发生
So, impact is when my diet ends.
‎只不过我没有在减肥 ‎我只是一天哭五次而已
Only I'm not on a diet. I'm just crying five times a day.
‎-我很害怕 ‎-嘿 过来
-I'm scared. Hey, come on. Come on.
‎现在大家都应该很恐慌 好吗？
Everyone should be panicking right now, okay?
‎-别哭 拜托 ‎-我知道
-Don't cry. Come on. I know.
‎那个混蛋！
That prick!
‎（你认识那个 ‎说我们都要死了的疯女人吗？）
‎（我和她睡过）
‎怎么了？
What happened?
‎我男朋友好像刚跟我分手了
Guess my boyfriend just broke up with me.
‎天啊 今天真难熬
-God, what a day. What a day…
‎你会死的！你也会死的！你也…
You're gonna die! You're gonna die! You're…
‎起因是一张被很多人看成腋下
It started with a photo many thought was an armpit
‎或是长着奇怪胡须的男人下巴的照片
or the chin of a man with a strange beard.
‎结果竟是一桩丑闻…
But what's emerging now is a scandal…
‎奥尔林总统给一位最高法院提名人
President Orlean sent her Supreme Court nominee
‎发送了自己私处的手机照片
a cell phone picture of her private parts.
‎-天啊！ ‎-这是骗点击的玩意
-Holy crap! It's clickbait material.
‎你们国家想要的是这种领导人吗？
Is this what you want in your country as a leader?
‎她不就是那个跟穷人说
Isn't she the same person who told poor people
‎不想受穷 ‎就选个好点的彩票号码的人吗？
that if they don't wanna be poor, they should pick better lottery numbers?
‎她真的说过
She actually said that.
‎还有线人和我说
A source also confirmed to me that
‎这两人偷情多年了
the two have been having an affair for years.
‎就在昨天…
And as recently as yesterday…
‎我党成员正在起草 ‎针对总统的正式谴责
Members of my party are currently drawing up a formal censure
‎贾妮奥尔林…
of the president, Janie Orlean…
‎哦 天啊 亲爱的
Oh, my God, honey.
‎这个人连日心轨道是什么都不知道
This guy doesn't even know what a heliocentric orbit is,
‎他还管我叫怪人
and he's calling me a crackpot.
‎他说
He says that,
‎“犹太富豪编造了这个彗星威胁
"Jewish billionaires invented this comet threat
‎好让政府没收我们的自由和枪支”
so the government can confiscate our liberty and our guns. "
‎“话题标签 别害怕” 难以置信
"#DontBeScared. " Unbelievable.
‎我的天
My God.
‎你最近总看这个网站
You've been on that site a lot lately.
‎是啊 亲爱的 我有25万订阅用户
Yeah. I mean, I… I have, like, a quarter million subscribers, honey.
‎我得用自己的声音传播真相 对吧？
I gotta use my voice to get the truth out there, right?
‎我要去散步 一起来吗？
I'm, uh, going for a walk if you wanna come.
‎这叫科学方法 ‎就是科学方法创造了电脑
It is called the scientific method… …and it is what created the computer
‎结果你用电脑来打字 ‎传播你那愚蠢的阴谋论
that you are typing your half-witted conspiracy theories on.
‎你觉得如何？
What do you think about that?
‎兰德尔？
Randall?
‎-怎么了 亲爱的？ ‎-有人找你
-Yeah, honey? Someone's here to see you.
‎谁？哦 天啊
Who? Oh, boy.
‎哦 我的天
Oh, my gosh.
‎哦 老天 好吧
Oh, God, right. Okay.
‎好
Right.
‎你是兰德尔明迪博士？
Are you Dr. Randall Mindy?
‎是我 先生
Yes, sir. I am.
‎“我们都会死”
"We're all gonna die. "
‎滚开
Fuck off, please.
‎联邦调查局！不许动！ ‎马上跪下！跪下！
FBI! Freeze! Get on your knees right now! Get on your knees!
‎你因泄露国家机密被捕了
You're under arrest for breach of national security secrets.
‎老天爷啊！
Jesus Christ!
‎你们打电话给我或者去我家就好了
You could've just called me or showed up to my apartment.
‎你这是干什么 打扮成盲人？
What are you, dressed up as a blind guy?
‎-趴在地上！ ‎-好 冷静点
Get on the ground! Okay. Now be cool.
‎我只是肤色比你深一点而已
I just have more skin pigmentation than you.
‎因为你的祖先迁徙到了北欧
'Cause your ancestors migrated to Northern Europe
‎进化出了更浅的肤色 为了…
and developed lighter skin so as to not get…
‎除非你们这些混蛋要带我去蝙蝠洞
Unless you assholes are taking me to the Batcave,
‎不然去你妈的 竟给我戴头套
fuck you for putting this hood on me.
‎提防他一点 ‎他会拿免费的东西来向你收钱
Watch out for him. He'll charge you for free shit.
‎他来干什么？他跟我们一起的吗？
What's he doing here? Is he here for us?
‎先生们 可以进来了
Gentlemen, you can come in.
‎我想应该是温斯顿丘吉尔…
I think it was Winston Churchill who…
‎或者是鲍勃奈特说过 ‎“伟大的领导力会令
Or maybe it was Bobby Knight who said, "The great labor of leadership
‎自尊的束缚得到解脱
is to lay down one's yoke of pride
‎犯过的错误得到承认”
and admit that mistakes were made. "
‎你们被误导了 我也是
You were deceived, as was I,
‎但结果是这样的 我们找了
but the end result was, we had our scientists who went to
‎哈佛、普林斯顿等名校毕业的科学家
, uh, the prestigious schools of Harvard, Princeton, et cetera.
‎确认了这些数据
They confirmed the data.
‎我们想向你们
So we would like to offer you a…
‎表示来自总统的歉意
presidential apology.
‎-真的吗？ ‎-你听到了吗？
Really?
‎我们已经完全准备好动员起来
And we are fully prepared to mobilize
‎以前所未有的方式拯救地球
in historic fashion in order to save this planet.
‎这是这么长时间以来 ‎听到的最好的消息
The best news we've heard in a long time.
‎你的意思其实是 ‎你就要输掉中期选举了
So, basically, what you're saying isyou're about to lose the midterms 'cause you got caught
‎因为你被抓到发私密图
sending pictures of your cooch
‎给你的毛片主演警长男友
to your porn-star sheriff boyfriend.
‎所以现在对彗星采取行动 ‎对你有好处？
So now it's to your advantage to act on the comet?
‎对的
Right.
‎好吧
Okay.
‎好 我只是…
Okay. I'm just…
‎天啊 你们总算要做点什么了 ‎我松了口气
God, I'm so relieved that you guys are doing something.
‎-嘿 过来 嘿 ‎-这真的…
-Hey, come on. Hey. This has been really…
‎-真的很难熬 ‎-过来
Really, really hard. Come here.
‎这对我们来说都太有压力了
This has been really, really, really stressful on all of us.
‎是 我同意
Yes, I will agree.
‎这让我们所有人都如释重负…
This will take some heavy weight off all of us--
‎抱歉 你哭起来太难看了
Sorry, you just look so bad when you cry.
‎也许
Maybe, possibly.
‎人们会问我们为什么没有早点行动
People are gonna ask why we didn't act earlier.
‎这事你要背锅
So you're gonna have to take the hit on this one.
‎对 但我们将来会照顾好你的 乔斯林
Yeah, but we'll take care of you down the road, Jocelyn.
‎-我们会的 ‎-当然 贾妮
-We will. Of course, Janie.
‎我明早就会引咎辞职
I will resign in disgrace first thing tomorrow.
‎-很好 ‎-太奇怪了
Good. Yeah, good. That's weird as hell.
‎她是个麻醉师
She's an anesthesiologist.
‎我会发声明
I'm going to make a statement,
‎向美国人民发一份总统声明
presidential statement to the American people.
‎我们不会提前告诉媒体
And we're not gonna tell the press about it ahead of time
‎因为这样看起来就会像
because that way it will have the appearance
‎突发的紧急情况…
of a breaking emergency sort of…
‎有耐心的人总会等到好事
Good things come to those who wait.
‎你看？
See? Whoo!
‎哦 我的天！
Oh, my God!
‎（紧急广播系统）
‎我们打断《金龟婿》的播出
We interrupt this broadcast of Jackpot Fiancé
‎插播一条来自美国总统的紧急信息
for an emergency message from the president of the United States.
‎美国公民以及全世界人民们
Citizens of the United States and peoples of the world,
‎我刚收到
I have just been handed
‎一份科学发现 ‎证实了一个最糟糕的情况
scientific findings that confirm a worst-case scenario.
‎一颗九公里宽的前所未有的彗星
An unprecedented comet, nine kilometers wide,
‎现在正向我们宝贵的家园地球撞来
is now on a direct collision course with our cherished home, planet Earth.
‎预计到达时间约为五个月后
Estimated time of arrival is approximately five months from now.
‎所以我们…
So we have…
‎我们已经做好了 ‎一份巨额国会开支账单…
We've drawn up a massive Congressional spending bill…
‎我已经为国会 ‎准备了一份紧急开支方案…
I have already put together an emergency spending package for Congress…
‎…参议院及众议院均已通过
…that the Senate and the House have agreed upon.
‎很好
That's good to hear.
‎这将支持美国国家航空航天局 ‎和我们伟大的军队
And that will enable NASA and our great military
‎发起一次抢先撞击
to launch a preemptive strike,
‎利用退役的航天飞机和卫星
using decommissioned space shuttles and satellites
‎装载核弹
loaded with nuclear explosives.
‎我们将会 ‎把迪比亚斯基彗星撞离原有轨道…
We will blow Comet Dibiasky off her course…
‎但我们需要一位英雄
But we're gonna need a hero.
‎我们需要一位飞行员 真枪实弹…
We're gonna need a pilot, real guns and…
‎这项任务不该使用远程技术完成吗？
Shouldn't this mission be accomplished using remote technology?
‎华盛顿永远需要英雄
Washington's always gotta have a hero.
‎我邀请
I have asked
‎自由勋章获得者、心直口快的爱国者 ‎本尼迪克特德拉斯克
Medal of Freedom recipient and outspoken patriot, Benedict Drask,
‎承担这项艰难而…
to undertake this difficult and…
‎不好意思 这不是那个
I'm sorry. Isn't he the mercenary gentleman
‎在白宫草坪上吼小孩的雇佣兵吗？
that was screaming at all those children on the White House lawn?
‎对 他曾有幸执行总统发起的
Yeah. He was given the honor of leading
‎让儿童锻炼身体的活动
the presidential initiative in getting kids to exercise.
‎跳高一点 你们这些胖子…
Get a little air into it, you lard-ass…
‎你们就像一群胆小鬼
You look like a goddamn bunch of pussies.
‎-抱歉 ‎-我觉得他是上一代人的思维
I'm sorry. He's just of another generation.
‎我以前和他谈过恋爱
You know, I used to date him.
‎知道以前我在战斗中 ‎遇到的最后一个懦夫怎么样了吗？
Know what happened to the last pussy I worked with in combat?
‎看过人体内部是什么样吗？
You ever see inside a man's torso?
‎本尼迪克特德拉斯克前来报到
Benedict Drask reporting for duty.
‎-感谢你… ‎-他很棒的
-Thank you for the… He's gonna be fantastic.
‎他声音很好听
He's got a great voice.
‎-我们要让他发表一份声明 ‎-有人说这是一个…
-We're gonna let him make a statement. Some are saying this is a…
‎他身材也很好
He's got a great body too.
‎-真的 ‎-是啊
He does. Yeah.
‎…自杀任务
…suicide mission.
‎我唯一的要求是
Well, all I ask is,
‎如果我死了
if I get snuffed,
‎你们都能因我的牺牲而活得更久
that you all earn the extra living my sacrifice gives you.
‎因我的牺牲让他们活得更久
The extra living my sacrifice gives them.
‎-对吧？ ‎-这是我写的
-Right? I wrote that.
‎这不是《拯救大兵瑞恩》的台词吗？
Isn't that from Saving Private Ryan?
‎-是的 ‎-不 那里面的台词完全不一样
-Yes. No, that's something totally different.
‎特别感谢我身后的科学家团队…
And special thanks should also go to this team of scientists behind me…
‎这次任务 我们需要所有人的帮助
We're gonna need everybody's help on this.
‎-所有人 ‎-…关于这场迫在眉睫的威胁
Everybody.
‎所有人都应行动起来 ‎把这条消息传播出去
All have to pitch in and push out this message.
‎…非裔美籍科学家
…African-American scientist.
‎迪比亚斯基小姐 她…
Miss Dibiasky, she…
‎彗星就是以她命名的 ‎凯特迪比亚斯基
And we have Kate Dibiasky, who the comet is named after,
‎但不要责怪她
but don't blame her.
‎…和不满的年轻人、精神疾病
…connects with the disaffected youth and the mentally ill.
‎-以及其他边缘群体产生共鸣 ‎-谢谢
-And other marginal groups. Thank you.
‎-我们会尽己所能 ‎-只要你们采取正确的行动
We'll do whatever we can. As long as you do the right thing.
‎-我们会支持你们的 ‎-好
We're there for you.
‎特别是你 明迪博士 ‎因为你的民调结果远高于你的同事们
Especially you, Dr. Mindy, because you poll so much higher
‎很疯狂
than your colleagues. It's wild.
‎他会帮助我们 ‎摧毁我们共同的敌人 迪比亚斯基
He will help us destroy our common enemy, Dibiasky.
‎真棒 我想我们的工作结束了
Wonderful. Well, I think we're done.
‎是的 好 我们走吧
Yep, okay. Let's go.
‎-我能说句话吗？ ‎-凯特…
Can I say something?
‎我们等不及想听你的发言呢
We've been dying to hear what you gotta say.
‎我没有投票给你
I didn't vote for you.
‎但这件事比我对你的怀疑重要很多
But this is obviously much bigger than my misgivings.
‎我会全力支持的
So I will be 100% behind this effort.
‎无论我觉得你有多无礼
No matter how offensive I may find you.
‎哇 太棒了
Hmm. Wow. That's great.
‎是啊 真好
Yeah. That's really nice.
‎是我让联邦调查局的人套住你的头
You know, I did have the FBI put that bag over your head.
‎他们一般不那么做 ‎中情局才会这样 但我要求他们做了
They don't do that. The CIA does, but I made them do it.
‎我其实猜到了 真的
You know, I had a feeling. I really did.
‎猜得很准 这就是我的行事风格
It's a good feeling 'cause that is what I did.
‎-很有趣 很酷 ‎-好的
-And it was very funny and cool. Okay.
‎愿耶稣基督保佑你们每个人
May Jesus Christ bless every single one of you,
‎特别是我党光荣的成员们
especially the honorable members of my own party.
‎我们会胜利的
We will prevail.
‎我们都会死！
-We're all gonna die!
‎各位 这颗彗星让我压力好大
Guys, this comet is seriously stressing me out.
‎它要来了 人们应该挖防御沟渠
Well, it's coming. People gotta dig in.
‎已经有人在线上市场找我买铁铲
I already got buyers for these shovels on e-market.
‎奥尔林总统在中期选举中 ‎取得压倒性胜利
Clean sweep for President Orlean in these midterm elections.
‎（奥尔林支持率99. 1%）
‎-说到他的性感 ‎-一张照片一千块
…how hot he is. Thousand bucks a pop.
‎（天文女巫 谴责凯特）
‎（彗星是场骗局吗？）
‎-我们突然就要完蛋了！ ‎-“…履行我即将承担的职责”
…discharge the duties on which I am about to enter.
‎“向上帝起誓”
"So help you God. "
‎-向上帝起誓 ‎-祝贺
-So help me God. Congratulations.
‎（股票市场暴涨！）
‎办公室在严肃讨论颁出诺贝尔和平奖
We have talk of a Nobel Peace Prize in the offing.
‎他不性感啊
He's not hot.
‎（股票市场下跌 一日破纪录！）
‎（末日将近 还会有超级碗吗？）
‎你好 胡麻
Hello, Sammy.
‎你真的是个博士吗？
Are you really a doctor?
‎算是吧 我是个天文学家
Well, sort of. I'm an astronomer.
‎天文学家是什么？
Oh. What is an astronomer?
‎明迪博士 很多人非常恐惧
Dr. Mindy, there is a lot of fear out there,
‎在美国 乃至全世界
uh, in America, around the world.
‎家长们不知道该怎么和孩子们说
Parents don't know what to say to their kids.
‎你有什么话可以 ‎帮助他们理解现在的处境吗？
What would you say to them to help them understand?
‎我知道现在很多人一定很害怕
Well, I'm sure many of us are frightened right now.
‎但我向大家保证 ‎最优秀、最聪明的人正在着手解决
But I can assure you, our best and our brightest, they're on the job.
‎我看过这个计划的科学论证 ‎非常可靠
I've seen the science on this plan and it is sound.
‎我知道你的话一定能 ‎安慰到我们所有观众 兰德尔博士
I know your words are a great comfort to all our viewers, Dr. Randall,
‎我们感谢你的勇气和贡献
and we thank you for your courage and your service.
‎我想说
I'd just like to say
‎每当我感到害怕或孤独 我…
that whenever I feel afraid or alone in this, I…
‎只要想到你 我就会好受些 谢谢
I think of you and I just… I feel better.
‎这是我的工作
So thank you. That's my job.
‎-给我说我们都会死 ‎-什么？
-Tell me we're all gonna die. What?
‎-说吧 我们都会死 快 ‎-我们都会死
-Tell me we're all gonna die, do it. We're all gonna die.
‎哦 天啊
Oh, boy.
‎所以这两个马克思主义者 ‎挥舞着“科学”二字
So, these two Marxists wave around the word "science"
‎我们就应该照他们说的做？
and we're all supposed to do whatever they say?
‎我们怎么知道是不是真的有彗星？
Yeah, how do we know there even is a comet?
‎众议员帕凯蒂先生 这份数据已经由
Mr. Pawketty, Congressman, this data has been proven
‎数百名世界知名科学家证实和审校过
and has been peer-reviewed by hundreds of world-renowned scientists.
‎我们应该相信你？ ‎彗星可是用你的名字命名的
And we're supposed to trust you? The comet's got your name.
‎我不明白这有什么关联
I don't… I don't see the relevancy.
‎那为什么不回答一下问题？
Why won't you answer the question?
‎-回答问题 ‎-问题是什么？
-Answer the question. What's the question?
‎成熟一点 可以吗？
Grow up here, okay?
‎太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
‎我刚意识到 ‎我们一点都不了解彼此 是不是？
I've just realized, we don't really know anything about each other. Do we?
‎是的
True.
‎每次我试着问关于你生活的问题
Well, every time I try to ask you about your life,
‎你好像只会告诉我你喜欢的餐厅
you seem to just tell me about your favorite restaurants.
‎我…你懂的…
Well, I… You know…
‎我不喜欢感情中
I just despise the, you know,
‎互相了解这个步骤 所以…
getting-to-know-you part of relationships, so…
‎好吧 我理解
Oh, okay. I understand.
‎好吧 那么我们速战速决
Okay, let's just get it over and done with.
‎好的
Okay, uh…
‎对…
Right, so, uh…
‎我祖父发明了速冻技术
My grandfather invented the flash-freezing process.
‎所以我家境非常好
So I come from grotesque money,
‎但我远离家业 拿了三个硕士学位
but I got away from it by getting three masters degrees.
‎我离过两次婚
Uh, I've been divorced twice.
‎一次是和一个国务卿 ‎另一次是和一个游钓运动员
Uh, one was a Secretary of State, and the other one was a sport fisherman.
‎我睡过两个前总统
Uh, I have slept with two former presidents.
‎我会说四种语言 有两幅莫奈的画
I speak four languages, and I own two Monets.
‎哇
Wow.
‎两个前总统 哇
Two former presidents. Wow.
‎-到我了？ ‎-对
-What, my turn? Yeah.
‎好吧 我爸是个中学地理老师
Oh. All right. My father was a middle school geography teacher.
‎我妈在厨房外面给人理发
My mother, she cut hair out of the kitchen.
‎大约两年前 我们家的狗 乔乔死了
Uh, about two years ago, our family dog, JoJo, died,
‎这让人很难过
which was really, really emotional.
‎我记忆中从未哭过那么厉害
I can't remember crying that much ever.
‎还有…
And, um…
‎我终于拿到了 ‎马克哈米尔签名的《星球大战》海报
I finally got my, uh, Star Wars poster signed by Mark Hamill.
‎在车库里…对
It's in the garage. It's… So, yeah.
‎好的 很好
Okay, good.
‎结束了
That's done. Ah…
‎我们今晚去哪儿吃？
Where are we gonna go for dinner tonight?
‎（发射日）
‎耶和华是我的牧者 我必不至缺乏
The Lord is my shepherd. I shall not want.
‎他使我躺卧在青草地上
He makes me to lie down in green pastures.
‎（东部中午12点23）
‎领我在可安歇的水边 ‎他使我的灵魂苏醒
He leads me beside the quiet waters. He restores my soul.
‎诺曼底登陆以来 ‎我们还没见过如此大规模调动
Not since D-Day have we seen such a mass mobilization
‎队伍和资源的神圣任务
of unions and resources for such a noble task.
‎即便是无法帮上忙的人们
One cannot help but be moved by the bravery, ingenuity,
‎也会被这里展现出的勇气 ‎智慧和牺牲所感动
and sacrifice on display here.
‎好了各位 大家保持警惕
Okay, here we go, everyone. Let's stay sharp.
‎我希望你知道 这是至今为止发生过
I just want you to know, this is the most propulsive thing
‎对我助益最大的事情 谢谢
that's ever happened to me. Thank you.
‎你们等什么呢？各位？
What's the holdup, you guys? What are you waiting on?
‎拜托 混蛋们 把烟花点燃吧
Come on, motherfuckers, let's light this fucking firecracker, huh?
‎当我很有空吗？
Think I got all day?
‎德拉斯克长官 这里是总统
Commander Drask, this is your president speaking.
‎你的国家感谢你
Your nation thanks you.
‎你的星球感谢你
Your planet thanks you.
‎我和上帝感谢你
And God and I thank you.
‎听着 我需要的谢礼 ‎只有一杯杰克丹尼尔
Listen, the only thanks I need is a shot of Jack Daniels.
‎和撤销几条酒驾记录
And a couple DUIs to magically go away.
‎这里是指挥中心 所有指标正常
This is Mission Control. All indicators are coming up green.
‎这是控制发射台的最后警告
This is a final warning to control the launchpad.
‎是你们的发现带来了 ‎这次任务以及让我们拯救地球的机会
Your discovery led to this mission and our chance to save Earth.
‎我要给予你们…
I give you…
‎这份荣誉
the honor.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎谢谢你 总统女士
Thank you, Madam President.
‎地球公民们
Citizens of planet Earth,
‎任何事在完成之前
everything is theoretically impossible
‎理论上都是不可能的
until it is done.
‎记住这一点 我们准备发射
And with that, we are go for launch.
‎好
Yes.
‎-太好了 ‎-谢谢
That's fire. Thank you.
‎非常好
It was lit.
‎你们不介意我加入吧？
Hey, everyone, mind if I join?
‎-大家好 ‎-你好 彼得
-Hello. Hello, Peter. Hi.
‎你好布里 你还是老样子 光彩照人
Hi. Oh, Brie, you look fabulous.
As always.
‎他可以进这里吗？
Is he allowed to be in here?
‎是的 他是竞选活动的 ‎白金雄鹰等级捐助者 可以畅通无阻
Yeah, he's a Platinum Eagle level donor to the campaign. He has full clearance.
‎部署发射任务
Launch mission array.
‎摇头丸开始生效了 时机刚刚好
Molly kicking in right now. Timed that shit perfect.
‎十、九、八、七、六、五、四…
Ten, nine, eight… seven, six, five, four…
‎三…
Three… Ah…
‎感谢上帝！
Thank God!
♪ Oh, Susannah Don't you cry for me ♪
♪ I come from Alabama With a banjo on my knee, hey! ♪
‎没有失去任何卫星
We didn't lose any satellites.
‎容错空间是两台故障
Margin of error was for two to malfunction.
‎嘿 总统女士 ‎可以和你出来说句话吗？
Hey, Madam President, may I have a word with you outside for a moment, please?
‎哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
‎任务成功的概率已经提升到81%
Mission success probability is already increased to 81%.
‎真出色
Outstanding.
‎贾妮 马上！
Janie, now!
‎太抱歉了
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
‎彼得 我不是故意…
Peter, I didn't mean…
‎向这颗我们所有人 ‎称之为故乡的美丽的蓝色星球问好
And a big hello to that beautiful blue ball down there we all call home.
‎还有所有那些 ‎努力工作的骄傲的白人
All those proud white folks working hard.
‎上帝保佑你们
God bless you.
‎这只是代沟吧 是的
Just a different generation. Yeah.
‎我还要和所有印第安人打招呼
I also wanna say hello to all the Indians out there.
‎还有印度人 骑大象的和拿弓箭的
Both kinds. You know, the ones with the elephants and the ones with the bow and arrows.
‎嘿 你们为什么不联合起来？ ‎那该多棒啊？
Hey, why haven't you guys ever teamed up? How cool would that be, huh?
‎我想和所有同性恋打个招呼
I wanna say hello to all the gays out there.
‎长官 助推器即将弹射
-Commander, booster ejection is imminent. Huh?
‎-我们继续沟通任务内容吧 ‎-收到
-Let's keep comm on mission. Oh. Roger that.
‎分离确认
Separation confirmed.
‎好
-Separation confirmed. Whoo!
‎那是法语吗？
Was that French?
‎是的 意思是“天使们飞往天堂”
Yes, it is. It means, "the angels soar to the heavens. " It's, um…
‎这是我在达特茅斯学过的 ‎一首14世纪诗歌
It's from a 14th-century poem I studied in Dartmouth.
‎看着这场面 让我想到了它
And just watching this, it just made me think of it,
‎想到了你
and think of you.
‎天啊 我不能…
God, I can't…
‎不能…
Can't…
‎（#发射挑战）
Go! Go! Go!
‎我觉得我可能应该去医院看看…
I think I probably should go to the hospital and see what they…
‎来吧！
Launch challenge!
‎发射！
Go! Go! Go!
‎各位 我刚收到
Everyone, I have just received
‎一些关于我们任务的重要信息
some critical information concerning our mission.
‎看起来好像调头了
Looks like it's turning around.
‎不 没有 这是轨道纠偏
No, it's not. It's a course correction.
‎是标准流程
It's pretty standard.
‎我以前在海军待过
I was in the Navy.
‎不 它调头了
Nope. It's turning around.
‎看来人群有些困惑
Seems to be some confusion here amongst the crowd,
‎但我和大家说实话
but I'm not gonna lie to you.
‎此刻记者也无语了
This reporter is at a loss for words right now.
‎它真的调头了
It's definitely turning around.
‎我正看着它
I'm looking straight at it.
‎德拉斯克的飞船肯定是掉头了
Drask's ship is definitely turning around.
‎有人知道刚才发生了什么吗？
Does anyone know what the fuck just happened?
‎还是锁着的
It's still locked.
‎我不明白有可能出什么事
I just don't… I don't understand what could've happened.
‎任务当时进行顺利 ‎是不是？一切正常
I mean, the mission was working, right? Everything was on track.
‎是啊 一切皆有可能
Yeah. I mean, it could've been anything, uh…
‎也许导航系统故障了 核弹不稳定 ‎很多可能性
Guidance system could've malfunctioned, uh, nuke destabilized, myriad of things.
‎走进战情室的那个男人是谁？
Who was that guy that walked into the Situation Room?
‎看起来很眼熟
He looked familiar.
‎那是彼得伊舍威尔 巴什公司 ‎首席执行官 史上第三富有的人
That was Peter Isherwell, CEO of BASH, and the third richest human ever.
‎他就是那个买了《古登堡圣经》 ‎又把它弄丢的人
He's the guy that, uh, bought the Gutenberg Bible and lost it.
‎抱歉让你们久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.
‎计划赶不上变化
Things are, uh, extremely fluid.
‎兰德尔博士
Dr. Randall,
‎你现在是白宫首席科学顾问
you are now the Chief Science Advisor to the White House.
‎什么？
What?
‎你需要参加一个紧急内阁会议
As such, you need to attend an emergency Cabinet meeting
‎会上你会知晓所有细节
where you will be debriefed.
‎那我们呢？
What about us?
‎你没有权限参加 宝贝 别嗑药了
You do not have clearance for this, sweetheart. Don't trip.
‎给你们拿了点薯片和水
Got you some crackers, some waters.
‎你没必要扔地上
You don't need to throw it on the floor.
‎最多三四个小时
Gonna be three, four hours, tops.
‎给 凯特 我不明白 ‎他为什么要扔地上 给
Here, Kate. I don't know why he threw 'em down. Here.
‎我们如果要去洗手间怎么办？
What if we have to go to the bathroom?
‎我们会给你们铺点报纸
We'll lay out some newspaper for you.
‎给你们拿一罐除臭剂
Grab you a can of Febreze.
‎-简短美好的步骤 对 ‎-我马上回来
Short, sweet and simple science.
‎好了 走吧
I'll be back. All right. Come on.
‎科学揭示真相 兰德尔
Science tells the truth, Randall.
‎可恶 你想来吗？
Fuck. Do you wanna come?
‎想啊
Yeah.
‎女士们先生们 我们以为
Ladies and gentlemen, what we thought,
‎全世界以为的这场紧迫、可怕的危机
what the world thought was an impending and terrifying danger,
‎结果竟是一个令人激动的机会
turns out to be an astonishing opportunity.
‎我们的盟友们非常困惑 正寻求解释…
Our allies are very confused and demanding answers--
‎让他们等着
Well, tell 'em to wait.
‎根据迪比亚斯基彗星 ‎最新的光谱仪检测数据
According to the most recent spectrometer readings of Comet Dibiasky,
‎由巴什蜂窝的天文学家算出
made by the astrogeologists at BASH Cellular,
‎我们有了新的发现
we've discovered something.
‎一些奇迹般的发现
Something truly miraculous.
‎彼得？
Peter. Peter?
‎谢谢你 贾妮
-Oh, thank you, Janie.
‎如你们中有些人所知
As, uh… As some of you may know,
‎世界上最珍贵的矿产
the most valuable minerals in the world
‎快速变成了
are fast becoming those that are deployed
‎用来制造手机和电脑的物质
in the manufacture of cell phones and, uh, computers.
‎钇、铽、锇、镝等等
Yttrium, terbium, osmium, dysprosium, on and on and on.
‎资源短缺
We're running short.
‎这个问题变得更加严重是因为
Uh, and the problem is exacerbated, of course,
‎中国掌握着几乎所有
because China has her big panda paw firmly on almost all the mines
‎出产这些宝贵稀缺地球资源的矿
that produce these valuable rare Earth assets.
‎你们可以想象
So you can imagine.
‎哇！
Wow!
‎我们巴什公司高兴极了
Just how happy we were at BASH
‎因为我们的天文学家发现
when our astrogeologists discovered
‎这颗从宇宙深处 ‎朝地球急速飞来的彗星
and then determined that this comet, hurtling towards us from deep space,
‎蕴藏着价值至少 ‎32万亿美元的重要矿产
actually contains at least $32 trillion of these critical materials.
‎这对技术来说非常重要
Critical to technology.
‎-如果我们要继续… ‎-抱歉
If we're to proceed--
‎中止整个任务的原因
I'm sorry. Is that why you aborted this entire mission,
‎就是你们想开采彗星上的稀缺矿产？
is because you're trying to mine the comet for rare minerals?
‎明迪博士 我觉得我们应该等 ‎整个演讲结束后再提问
I think we should hold all questions
until the end of the presentation,
‎到时也许你的问题就已经得到了回答
and you might find that your questions are answered.
‎是的 总统女士
Yes, Madam President.
‎考虑其他金属的话 彗星实际蕴藏了
When you… When the other metals are factored in, the comet actually contains
‎价值近140万亿美元的资源
almost $140 trillion worth of assets.
‎140万亿
Buck-forty trilli.
‎嗯…
Yeah…
‎如果我们都要死了 ‎这些万亿美元又有什么意义？
What do these trillions of dollars even matter if we're all gonna die--
‎我也想问这个问题 贾妮
I was about to ask the same question, Janie.
‎为何不征求我们的意见？
Why weren't we consulted?
‎-恕我直言 总统女士… ‎-哦 不！
All due respect, Madam President…
‎-…这极其危险 ‎-如果我们既赚了钱又安然无恙呢？
Oh, no! What if we're rich and we're safe?
‎我在脑子里一遍遍回想
I've gone over it again and again and again in my head
‎我还是想不通
and I still can't make sense of it.
‎他是个三星中将 在五角大楼工作
He's a three-star general. He works at the Pentagon.
‎为什么要拿免费零食收我们的钱？
Why would he charge us for free snacks?
‎我有一次遇到了斯汀
One time, I met Sting,
‎我对天发誓 他就在我面前放了屁
and I swear to God, he farted right in front of me.
‎没有避开视线 也没有说“抱歉”
Didn't break eye contact and didn't even say "excuse me. "
‎关键是 他丝毫没有引起反感
And the thing is, he actually pulled it off.
‎因为我依然觉得他很有魅力
'Cause I still found him to be quite charming.
‎两位 我们得谈谈 我们走 马上
Guys, we have to talk. Come on, let's go. Come on, now.
‎太疯狂了 彻头彻尾的疯狂
It's insane. Like, completely insane.
‎根本不可能成功的
It will never work.
‎我和你的反应一模一样
I had the exact same reaction.
‎这可是一颗直径九公里的地球杀手
This is a nine-kilometer-wide planet-killer we're talking about,
‎不是在说漫游费
not roaming charges.
‎他们取消任务 我也很困惑、很愤怒
Look, I… I was confused and outraged that they turned this mission around too,
‎但他们的团队有斯坦福的盖里泰可蒙
but they've got Gary Talcamont from Stanford
‎和普林斯顿的丽莎伊内兹
and Lisa Inez from Princeton on their team.
‎这可是下一代最前沿的技术
I mean, this is next-generation cutting-edge technology.
‎一颗巨大的彗星显然对地球来说 ‎是存亡攸关的重大威胁
Obviously, one giant comet is a major and existential, uh, threat to our planet,
‎但我们可以应付30个小型流星体
but 30 smaller meteoroids, we can handle.
‎我们的必得机 ‎也就是巴什探索开采无人机
Our BEADS, that stands for BASH, uh, Explore and Acquire Drones,
‎如你们所见
that you see here,
‎将会把机体附着在彗星上
attach themselves to the comet
‎使用纳米技术进行扫描
and scan it with nanotechnology
‎该技术由诺贝尔奖得主
developed by Nobel Prize-winning scientist,
‎盖里泰可蒙开发
Dr. Gary Talcamont.
‎然后我们就立刻开采了吧？
And then we immediately deploy, don't we?
‎诺贝尔和波隆斯基奖得主
Nobel and Polonsky prize-winning scientist
‎科学家伊内兹博士的 ‎微标量子裂变爆炸物
Dr. Inez's micro-targeted, quantum fission, uh, explosives.
‎看 深入星体中…
You see, deep into the object…
‎伊内兹博士 你要来说明一下吗？
Dr. Inez, would you like to explain what's happening?
‎谢谢你 彼得
Thank you, Peter.
‎我们在欧洲核子研究中心的 ‎粒子加速器中
We've been developing phase-fission reactions
‎进行分段裂变反应
in the CERN particle accelerator
‎用于将彗星分裂成小块
that can splinter the comet into smaller pieces
‎且确保极致精确
with breathtaking accuracy.
‎这些碎片随后将被每台必得机 ‎进行转向和减速
These segments are then steered and decelerated by each BEAD
‎落入太平洋 等待美国海军舰队回收
into the Pacific Ocean for reclamation by waiting US Navy ships.
‎当这些…谢谢
And when these… Thank you.
‎当这些来自天堂的宝藏回收之后
And when these treasures from heaven are claimed,
‎我们所知的贫困 ‎社会不公、生物多样性的丧失
poverty as we know it, social injustice, loss of biodiversity,
‎所有这些各种各样的问题
all these multitudes of problems
‎都将成为过去
are just gonna become relics of the past
‎人类将大步穿过 ‎所罗门圣殿的铜柱 全身赤裸地
and humanity is gonna stride through the Pillars of Boaz and Jachin naked
‎迈入黄金时代的光辉…
into the the glory of a golden age…
‎这个纳米技术经过了同行评审吗？
And is this nanotech work peer-reviewed?
‎我还没看数据 但已经建模了
Well, I haven't reviewed the data, but it's been modeled.
‎有任何部分经过了同行评审吗？
Has any of this been peer-reviewed?
‎没有
Nope.
‎行星间、星际
Interplanetary, interstellar,
‎星系间都将有人类存在
intergalactic existence for the human race.
‎-托你吉言 ‎-我愿意加入
Your mouth to God's ear.
‎他们能从这颗彗星上 ‎获取的矿产和财富
I understand the wealth that they can extract from this comet,
‎可以终结世界饥饿
it can end world hunger.
‎哦 我懂了
Oh, I see.
‎-你们笑什么？ ‎-没错 不 我明白
-Why are you laughing? That's true. No, I see.
‎这是他们用来给闹剧打掩护的小借口
So that's the pretty little bow they're putting around this line of bullshit.
‎我猜他们还会说解放小狗
I bet they'll say freedom and puppies too.
‎-是啊 ‎-好吧
-All right. Yeah.
‎你们想让我退出任务？ ‎那我就退出 没关系
You want me to quit the mission? I'll quit the mission. That's fine.
‎但你们得明白 ‎现在这已经不受我们控制了
But you have to understand, this is now beyond our control.
‎权力都在他们手上
They have all the power.
‎你们希望谁来参与并确保
So who do you want in the actual room to make sure
‎整件事不会变成彻头彻尾的灾难？
this whole thing doesn't turn out to be a complete goddamn disaster?
‎杰森奥尔林？ ‎你们希望杰森奥尔林参与吗？
Jason Orlean? You want Jason Orlean in that room? Huh?
‎跟你说个新鲜事 ‎现在已经是彻头彻尾的灾难了
I have news for you. It's already a complete disaster.
‎他们在让一个山峰大小的彗星
They're talking about letting a comet the size of a mountain
‎撞击地球 就为了让一家 ‎手机公司的股票大涨特涨！
hit the planet to jack up a cell phone company's stock!
‎你的音量最好马上降个四五级
You better take that down about four or five notches now.
‎你刚才大叫 ‎是在说他们取消任务的原因吗？
Were you yelling about that mission?
‎和手机有什么关系？
Why were you talking about cell phones?
‎我的朋友只是在猜想
My friend was just theorizing as to what's going on.
‎我们也一头雾水
We're confused too.
‎你看上去有正规的白宫胸牌
That's an awfully official-looking White House badge you got there.
‎我不知道这是哪来的 不清楚
I don't know why I have this on.
‎告诉我们是怎么回事吧
Listen, just tell us what's going on.
‎我家三个小孩都被吓坏了 ‎告诉我们点信息吧
I got three scared kids at home. Just tell us something.
‎我理解 我也希望能分享信息 但…
I understand. I wish I could share information, but--
‎我们和你们是一样的 ‎我们有权知道！
We're people just like you. We deserve to know!
‎他们说得对 他们有权知道
They're right. They deserve to know.
‎你们真的想知道发生了什么吗？
Do you really wanna know what's going on?
‎-是的 ‎-请告诉我们
Yeah. Please.
‎-嘿 凯特 不要 ‎-凯特
Kate, don't. Kate. Kate.
‎他们在彗星上发现了稀奇的金银财宝
They found a bunch of gold and diamonds and rare shit on the comet.
‎所以他们要让它撞击地球
So they're gonna let it hit the planet
‎让一群富人变得更他妈富有！
to make a bunch of rich people even more disgustingly rich!
Fuck you!
‎不要录像！
No camera!
‎…我都说了 他们就是不听
…everything I could, they won't listen.
‎真是惊喜
Surprise, surprise.
‎我开始觉得你就是喜欢煽动人群
Now, I'm starting to think you just like riling people up.
‎很抱歉 凯特 真的
I'm so sorry, Kate. Really, I am.
‎哦 兰德尔 天啊
Oh, Randall. God.
‎布里埃文蒂呢？
Where's Brie Evantee?
‎你俩不是应该在
Shouldn't you two be playing footsie in a restaurant
‎只供应方块和海绵的餐厅调情吗？
that only serves cubes and foam?
‎她说得没错 ‎你的行为确实有些离谱了
Well, she ain't wrong. You did lose the thread in a big way.
‎那你们觉得该怎么办？网上请愿吗？
And what do you suggest we do? An online petition, huh?
‎你们想举着… ‎带着暴动人群高举抗议标牌？
You want to hold… Get a mob and hold up picket signs?
‎你们想推翻政府？看看现实吧
You wanna overthrow the government? I mean, look at this.
‎我看不见！我脑袋上套着袋子！
I can't! My head is in a bag!
‎对不起 明迪博士 ‎白宫希望她与外界隔离
Sorry, Dr. Mindy. White House wants her off the grid.
‎-拜托 听着… ‎-马上
-Come on, now. Look Now.
‎等等 什么意思？那是什么鬼？
Wait. What does that mean? What the hell does that mean?
‎-“与外界隔离”是什么意思？ ‎-嘿 凯特
-What does "off the grid" mean? Hey, Kate.
‎哦 天啊 凯特！你没事吧？
Oh, gosh. Kate! Are you okay?
‎什么都不重要了！比如虚拟货币！
‎泰迪 拜托！我有选择吗？
Teddy, come on! What choice do I have here?
‎人总是有选择的 兰德尔！
A man's always got choices, Randall!
‎有时候你得做对的选择！
Sometimes you just gotta choose the good one!
‎凯特兰迪比亚斯基小姐
Miss Katelyn Dibiasky,
‎你面临的指控是泄露国家安全机密
the charges against you are violation of national security secrets,
‎煽动暴乱 ‎和损坏博乔曼波虾公司私有财产
inciting a riot, and destruction of private property owned by Bojo Mambo's Shrimp LLC.
‎什么？我没有…
What? I didn't--
‎但是 司法部长愿意不起诉你
However, the Attorney General is willing to not pursue prosecution
‎条件如下
if you will agree to the following:
‎“停止在任何公共媒体上露面
"The suspension of all public media appearances
‎不发表和迪比亚斯基彗星 ‎以及巴什蜂窝相关的煽动性言论”
and incendiary language relating to Comet Dibiasky and BASH Cellular. "
‎行了 给我吧 我不在乎了
Fine. Give it to me. I don't give a shit anymore.
‎爸妈 回家真是太好了
Mom. Dad. I'm so glad to be home.
‎开门啊
Unlock the door.
‎不要谈政治 绝不
No politics. None.
‎你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
‎我和你爸支持 ‎彗星将会带来的工作机会
Your dad and I are for the jobs the comet will provide.
‎这个国家的分化已经很严重了
The divisions in this country are bad enough.
‎我们不希望这个家里还政见不一
We don't want more of that in our house.
Whoa!
‎-慢点 孩子们 ‎-抱歉 妈妈
-Slow down, kids. Sorry, Mom.
‎我为孩子们的未来感到担忧
I worry about my kids and their future.
‎是的 彗星会创造的工作听起来很棒
Sure, the jobs the comet's gonna create sound great.
‎但假如它不安全呢？
What if it's not safe?
‎现在 成千上万的人们 ‎有着相同的疑虑…
Right now, millions of you are having these same doubts and questions
‎（兰德尔明迪博士）
‎…对即将到来的彗星感到不安
about the approaching comet.
‎因此巴什蜂窝
That is why BASH Cellular
‎联合美国政府
in conjunction with the United States Government
‎新建了这条免费热线 ‎回答你们的所有疑问
is creating a new hotline, free of charge, to answer all of your questions.
‎谁知道呢？也许 ‎我是说也许 我们的某位科学家…
And who knows? Maybe, just maybe, one of our scientists…
‎谢谢你 夏伦 我感觉好多了
Thank you, Sharon. Makes me feel so much better.
‎…可以成为在动荡时期 ‎我们可以依靠的那个朋友
…can be that friend we all need to lean on during uncertain times.
‎拨打1-800-532-4500 ‎安抚您的情绪
Call 1-800-532-4500 for peace of mind.
‎仅支持巴什顾客拨打
Offer only available to BASH customers.
‎通话细节可能与其他下属公司共享 ‎用于提升您未来的用户体验
Details of your call may be shared with other subsidiaries
‎您需支付数据漫游费用
to enhance your customer experience. Data and roaming charges apply.
‎我以为他是大使 我就在恭维他
So, I thought he was the ambassador. I was just flattering him.
‎他是个服务生 ‎他现在自信心爆棚到德州那么大
Well, he was a waiter. Now he's got an ego the size of Texas.
‎哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
‎琼 你来干什么 亲爱的？
June, what, uh… What are you doing here, sweetie?
‎我感觉可能不对劲 所以就…
Had a feeling something was going on and just…
‎我们在聊重要的事情
Well, you know, we're discussing important business.
‎-这就是我们在做的事 ‎-是啊 真的非常重要
-That's what we're doing. Oh, yeah, that's really very important.
‎这段能跳过吗？ ‎就是你感觉自己很占理
Oh, can we just skip past this part, please?
‎而我们像犯了错一样 ‎夹着尾巴的戏码 太无聊了
Where you get to feel self-righteous and we put our tails between our legs. It is just so boring.
‎“太无聊”？
Oh, it's "so boring"?
‎你想跳过 ‎因为和我丈夫上床而内疚的部分？
You wanna skip the part where you feel bad for screwing my husband?
‎不 我不内疚
Oh… No, I don't feel bad.
‎我和兰德尔相处很愉快 ‎我觉得问题在于
Randall and I are having a wonderful time. So, I think the question is,
‎是我们继续共享美好时光 ‎还是你和他回威斯康辛？
do we keep having a wonderful time or does he go back with you to Wisconsin?
‎或者蒙大拿
Or Montana.
‎-密歇根？ ‎-密歇根
-Michigan? Michigan.
‎她说得对
You know, um… she is actually right.
‎这是唯一的问题 所以…
That's the only question. So…
‎琼 亲爱的
Well, June, sweetie…
‎有时候生活就是很复杂…
Sometimes in life things are, you know, they're complicated and they just--
‎好吧
Oh, okay.
‎真快
Oh, that was fast, um…
‎我走之前
Well, before I go, um,
‎教你一下
let me just give you some instructions
‎-如何照顾兰德尔 ‎-我很抱歉
on how to take care of Randall.
‎对 这是赞安诺 惊恐发作时吃的
Uh… Yeah, here's the Xanax he takes for his panic attacks.
‎哦 天啊
Oh, gosh.
‎这是消沉崩溃时吃的左洛复
Here's the Zoloft he takes for the crashing depressions.
‎最近不太发作了 好吧…
-Not so much recently. Okay, you know Oh!
‎真好 那太好了
Oh, good for you. Great.
‎这是治疗血压的
-Uh, this is for his blood pressure. Ow.
‎-不宁腿综合征 这个很有意思 ‎-天啊
-Restless leg syndrome, that's a fun one. God.
‎用来中和其他药物 ‎导致的增重的厌食剂
Oh. Appetite suppressant to counteract the weight gain from his other meds.
‎还有给这位 ‎美国最性感科学家的希爱力！
And, uh, for America's sexiest scientist, a bottle of goddamn Cialis!
‎天啊
Ow! Gosh.
‎再见 再见 兰德尔
Goodbye. Goodbye, Randall.
‎看来我只能跟儿子们说
I guess I'll just tell your sons
‎爸爸和我们电视里的女人上床了
that Dad's fucking the lady on our television.
‎琼 我…
June, I…
‎我真的有一瞬间觉得能行得通的
I really thought for a second that was gonna work out.
‎各位 他们想控制彗星 ‎创造更多工作
People, they wanna manage the comet to create jobs.
‎37%的人完全不希望彗星撞击
Thirty-seven percent don't want the comet to hit.
‎这个比例下降了三个点
That's actually down by three points.
‎23%的人认为根本没有彗星
And 23%, they don't think there's a comet at all,
‎这个数字在上涨
and that number is way up.
‎为什么比特币？老鼠币？
Not Bitcoin, RatCoin.
‎老鼠币
RatCoin.
‎是 我觉得如果你看下数字…
‎我想买这副墨镜
I'd like to buy these sunglasses.
‎你是那个在直播上 ‎说我们都会死的女孩？
You that girl from live TV who said we're all gonna die?
‎不是 你要买什么？
No. What's your purchase?
‎搞没搞错？
What the fuck?
‎-不 就是你 肯定是你 ‎-对 是我
-Yeah, that's you. It's definitely you. Yep, that's me.
‎不得了 你是真正的传奇 言出必行
Holy shit. You're a stone-cold legend. Word is bond.
‎我的滑板上有你的照片
I got a picture of you on my board.
‎他滑板上有你照片
Picture on his fucking board.
‎太棒了 你要买什么？
That's great. What's your purchase?
‎如果不买东西 请你离开队伍
If you don't have one, get out of line
‎给后面的顾客让位
and make room for other customers.
‎我可以用不色情的方式 ‎摸摸你的头发吗？
Can I touch your hair in a non-sexual way?
‎-滚开 ‎-伙计 有点…
-Get the fuck away from me. Oh, dude, have some… Um…
‎打给迪欧戈 他会吓死 ‎你能快速和我朋友打个招呼吗？
Call Diogo, he'll freak out. Will you say hi to my friend?
‎他超喜欢你 ‎我们爱你 我们不喜欢…
Dude, he's obsessed with you. We love you. We don't like…
‎我们也受不了奥尔林
Can't stand Orlean, either. Yo, yo, yo! Yo!
‎你好吗？哟 快看…
What's up? Yo, check out…
‎闭嘴 看看我们和谁在一起
Yo, shut the fuck up. Check out who we're with.
‎-哟 伙计！怎么样？ ‎-怎么样？
-Yo, bro! What up? What up?
‎我们要买东西 但我们没钱
I mean, we have a purchase, but we don't have payment,
‎也就是说…
which is a metaphor on…
‎-没现金？ ‎-而且 菲利普 我听说…
-Cash? Also, Phillip, I've been told…
‎-对 ‎-…你写了本书
-Right. …that you wrote a book
‎讲述你和凯特迪比亚斯基的旧情
about your past relationship with Kate Dibiasky.
‎你的说法很有意思 我还在写呢
Funny you should say that, I'm working on that now.
‎书名叫《与魔鬼擦肩而过》 而且…
It's gonna be called A Brush With The Devil, and it's, uh…
‎你是在用眼神呼叫保安吗？
You calling security or something, with your eyes?
‎不是 你们可以走了
No. You're free to go.
‎-听起来很不妙啊 ‎-就这样？
That sounds terrible. Just like that?
‎你不在乎吧？
You don't give a shit, do you?
‎我当然在乎
Sure, I do.
‎我在乎保障超市的品质服务
I care about DrinkMo's guarantee of quality service.
‎我们也不在乎
Well, we don't give a shit either.
‎一点也不在乎
Not one single shit.
‎我们七点后在废弃的汉堡皇背面玩
We hang and board behind the abandoned Burger Crown
‎滑滑板什么的
from 7:00 to whenever.
‎是的
Yeah, we do.
‎想来的话你也可以来 只要你敢
You should come hang. If you're not a fucking pussy.
‎那是我和…
Oh, you know, it's me…
‎-妈的 好 谢谢 ‎-…还有一瓶苏格兰威士忌
-Fuck. Okay. Thanks. …and a bottle of scotch.
‎开玩笑 但仍然…
It's a joke. But also…
‎（巴什）
‎好
Okay,
‎请让我向你们介绍
let me introduce you
‎人类的救星 巴什探索开采无人机
uh, to mankind's savior, BASH Explore and Acquire Drone.
‎难以置信
It's incredible.
‎很难以置信吧？
It's incredible, isn't it?
‎我管它叫一声部 第一台
I call this one Primo, the first.
‎就像我的第一个孩子一样
It's like my first child.
‎一声部 好孩子 ‎爸爸来了 我是克罗诺斯
Primo, my boy. It's your father, Cronos.
‎别害羞 过来 你将成为天上的神明 ‎我会照顾你的
Don't be shy. Come on. You're gonna be a god in the sky.
‎你考虑过必得机爆破的同步问题吗？
Are you at all concerned about the sync on the BEAD explosions?
‎哦 博士 人总会有疑问和恐惧…
Oh, Doctor. There are always questions and fears, and…
‎我有一份来自伊内兹博士的报告
I have a report here from a Dr. Inez.
‎-你可以看一下这份研究 ‎-谢谢
-If you'd just take a look at this study. Oh, thanks.
‎听着 我的很多同事
Listen, a lot of my colleagues,
‎要么是被调离 ‎要么是辞职离开这个项目
they've either been removed or resigned from this project,
‎显然都是因为问了太多 ‎和这个任务有关的问题
apparently for asking too many questions about this mission here.
‎我只想确认你…
So I just wanna make sure that you're…
‎你愿意接受科学同行评审的流程
That you're open to the scientific peer-review process
‎而不是以生意人的方式处理整个任务
and you're not approaching this mission like a businessman.
‎-就是… ‎-你说什么？
-You know? That What did you say?
‎-我想知道你是否… ‎-你说我是生意人？
-I wanna know if you're Did you call me a businessman?
‎-你确实有家公司… ‎-你觉得我只是个生意人？
-You do own a corporate You think I'm just a businessman?
‎你觉得你了解我吗 博士？
Do you think you know me, Doctor?
‎生意？
Business?
‎这是进化 这是人类的进化
This is evolution. This is evolution of the human species.
‎-你找这种人来是要… ‎-这个…
-What are you doing bringing this… Well--
‎你知不知道 ‎巴什有超过四千万个关于你的数据点
You know that BASH has over 40 million data points on you,
‎记录你1994年以来每个决策 博士
on every decision you have made since 1994, Doctor?
‎我比你的医生早几个月 ‎就知道你长了结肠息肉
I… I know when you have colon polyps
‎其实你现在就有四五个
months before your doctor does. You got four or five at the moment actually.
‎它们不是什么大问题 ‎但如果我是你 我会尽快去做检查
You know, they're not of concern, but I'd have a checkup as soon as you can.
‎但更重要的是 ‎我知道你是什么样的人
But much more importantly than that, I know what you are. I know who you are.
‎我的算法确定了 ‎八种基础消费者资料类型
My algorithms have determined eight fundamental consumer profile types.
‎你是个生活方式理想主义者
You are a lifestyle idealist.
‎你觉得自己受信仰驱动 ‎崇高的道德信仰
You think you're motivated by beliefs, high ethical beliefs.
‎但你只会逃避痛苦 贪图享乐
But you just run towards pleasure and away from pain.
‎和田鼠一样
Like a… Like a field mouse.
‎我只是想…
I'm just trying to…
‎我只是想确保 ‎这个项目的科学过程没有问题
I just wanna make sure that the science is sound on this project.
‎希望你明白 我是说…
I hope you understand--
‎我们的算法甚至可以预测你的死法
Our algorithms can even predict how you'll die.
‎准确率高达96. 5%
To 96… 96. 5% accuracy.
‎我们见面后我就去查了一下
I looked you up after we met.
‎你的死亡很平庸、很无聊
Your death was so unremarkable and boring.
‎我记不清细节了 但有一点
I can't remember the details, apart from one thing.
‎你会独自死去
You're gonna die alone.
‎独自一人
Alone.
‎失陪了 总统女士 ‎我还有工作要做 我会跟他聊的
If you'll excuse me, Madam President. I've got some work to do.
‎你在干什么啊？哦 我的天
What the hell are you doing?
‎我在努力履行职责
-My God. I was trying to do my job.
‎彼得喜欢你真是算你走运
You are just so lucky that Peter adores you.
‎（易燃）
‎你身边现在都是成年人了 兰德尔
You're with the grown-ups now, Randall.
‎我都不能继续关注这破事了！
I can't even follow this shit anymore!
‎-死胖子 ‎-死胖子！
‎是 我两周前看到他了
‎如果我没搞错 巴什公司让奥尔林
BASH got Orlean to pay the Chilean government, if I'm correct,
‎给智利政府付了900亿美元 ‎让海啸冲击他们国家的海岸
$90 billion to let the tsunami hit off the coast of the country.
‎你觉得这合理吗？
That sound right to you?
‎（我们都他妈要死了）
Isherwell built an underground bunker
‎伊舍威尔给他 ‎和他的管理层造了地堡
for him and all his executives.
‎不 我听说他们造了逃生飞船
No, I heard that they built an escape ship.
‎各位 真相比这悲伤得多
You guys, the truth is way more depressing.
‎他们甚至没有聪明到
They're not even smart enough to be
‎可以像你们描述的那样邪恶
as evil as you're giving them credit for.
‎-怎么了？ ‎-不要
Ugh! What? No.
‎妈的！你让我发疯 凯特
Fuck! You're driving me fucking crazy, Kate.
‎不管了 反正我们都要死了
Fuck it. We're all gonna die. ♪ …sun, ice cream ♪
♪ You smooth like felt Soft to the touch ♪
♪ You wear repellent Smell your scent from up above ♪
♪ Angel getting carried out the club ♪
♪ For slapping Harry Harry's just a mug ♪
‎（减肥倒计时 25天）
♪ I'm stood outside waiting Where you gone? ♪
♪ Cubicle lines Catch a cold, Jack Frost ♪
‎…电影将在
…movie will be released
‎部分人相信迪比亚斯基彗星 ‎将要撞击地球的那天上映
the day that some believe Comet Dibiasky will impact the planet.
‎据透露 电影堪称经典 布里
And the early word is it's already a classic, Brie.
‎是的 而且阵容群星闪耀
Oh, yes. Well, and what a stellar cast.
‎-德文 ‎-我喜欢德文彼得斯
-Devin. Yeah. I love Devin Peters.
‎-是的 ‎-很棒 他做什么都很好
He's great. Everything he does.
‎-叫什么名字来着？ ‎-叫《全面毁灭》
-What's it called again? It's called Total Devastation.
‎耗资三亿美元
-It cost $300 million to make. Whoo!
‎-这些电影啊… ‎-比你赚的还多
-I mean, these movies It's more than you earn.
‎可不是 我朋友法利看过了
Tell me about it. And my friend Farley, he saw it.
‎-他说特别有趣 是的 ‎-法利喜欢
-He said it's a ton of fun. That's right. Well, Farley likes it.
‎好吧 法利说的都对
All right, well, what Farley says goes.
‎不过首先
But, uh, first,
‎是的 从我的笑容可以猜到…
and yes, you can tell from my smile…
‎别闹了
Stop it.
‎美国最性感的科学家来了 ‎兰德尔博士 欢迎
That America's sexiest scientist is here. Dr. Randall. Welcome.
‎兰德尔博士 你好吗？
Dr. Randall, how are you, sir?
‎我很好 好得不能再好了
I'm--  I'm good. I'm gooder than good.
‎好了 兰德尔 ‎我们听说彗星并不存在
All right. So, Randall, we're hearing that there is no comet,
‎或者彗星存在 但这是好事 ‎又或者是坏事
or that there is a comet but it's a good thing or maybe it's a bad thing.
‎我们很困惑
We are so confused.
‎能帮帮我们吗 睿智的科学家？
So, could you please help us out here, you know, oh, wise scientist?
‎首先 布里 彗星当然存在
Well, first and foremost, Brie, um… …there most certainly is a comet.
‎好的
All right.
‎我们知道有这么一颗彗星 ‎因为我们有数据
And we know that there is a comet because we have the data.
‎最近 科学界越来越忧心忡忡
Um… There has been growing concern within the scientific community as of late.
‎同行评审流程是非常有必要的…
You see, the peer-review process is absolutely essential…
‎-如果巴什的股票… ‎-…这样我们才能获取事实…什么？
-If BASH's stock… …for us to get to the facts of… Yes?
‎如果巴什的股票算一个指标的话
If BASH's stock is any indicator,
‎那我们就不用操心同行评审了
we don't have to worry about the peer review.
‎股票涨势爆棚
It is going gangbusters.
‎听我说 我全盘托出 ‎我尽可能买了很多股份
And full disclosure. I bought as many shares as I could.
‎我建议你们都这么做
I advise you to do the same.
‎你真是个无耻的资本家
You are such a shameless capitalist.
‎这个会躺在我家后露台的全新浴缸里 ‎泡在我从股市
Said the woman who will be in the brand-new hot tub on my back deck
‎-取出的钞票里的女人如是说 ‎-你太了解我了
-when I put it in from the stock. You know me too well.
‎没错
That's right.
‎兰德尔博士 你还好吗？ ‎要不要喝口水…
Dr. Randall, you sure you're okay? You want a glass of water…
‎我不太舒服
I don't feel so good.
‎好吧 我想我们先进一段广告…
So I think we'll go to commercial break--
‎不 拜托 布里 ‎别断开直播 让我说几句话
No, Please, Brie. Don't cut away. Let me say something.
‎-好的 ‎-那你来对地方了
-Okay. You came to the right place.
‎因为这节目里 我们就喜欢说话
We like to say things.
‎你能不能别一直这么…愉快？
Would you please just stop being so pleasant?
‎不好意思 ‎但不是所有事情都需要抖机灵
I'm sorry, but not everything needs to sound so goddamn clever
‎变幻出迷人讨喜的感觉
or charming or likeable all the time.
‎有时候我们需要能和彼此讲道理
Sometimes we need to just be able to say things to one another.
‎要把别人的话听进去
We need to hear things.
‎我们再重申一次
Look, let's establish, once again,
‎确实有一颗巨型彗星正朝地球飞来
that there is a huge comet headed towards Earth.
‎我们之所以知道有这样一颗彗星
And the reason we know that there is a comet
‎是因为我们看到了
is because we saw it.
‎我们用望远镜亲眼看到了
We saw it with our own eyes using a telescope.
‎老天啊 我们他妈的还拍了照！
I mean, for God's sake, we took a fucking picture of it!
‎我们还需要什么证据？
What other proof do we need?
‎如果我们连这都不能达成一致
And if we can't all agree at the bare minimum
‎同意一颗和珠穆朗玛峰一样大的彗星
that a giant comet the size of Mount Everest
‎朝地球呼啸而来他妈的不是件好事
hurtling its way towards planet Earth is not a fucking good thing,
‎那我们会有什么下场？
then what the hell happened to us?
‎我的天呐 我们要如何和彼此对话？
I mean, my God, how do How do we even talk to each other?
‎我们对自己做了什么？ ‎我们要如何弥补？
What've we… What've we done to ourselves? How do we fix it?
‎我们应该在 ‎还有机会的时候撞偏这颗彗星
We should have deflected this comet when we had the fucking chance,
‎但我们没有实施 我不知道为什么
but we didn't do it. I don't know why we didn't do it.
‎现在他们竟然还开除 ‎像我一样的科学家
And now they're actually firing scientists like me
‎就因为我们发声反对他们
for speaking out, for opposing them.
‎我知道很多人
And I'm sure many of the people out there
‎根本不会听我说的
aren't even gonna listen to what I just said
‎因为他们有自己的政治意识形态
'cause they have their own political ideology,
‎但我…我向你们保证
but I… assure you,
‎我不站在任何人的一边
I am not on one side or the other.
‎我只是他妈的把事实告诉你们
I'm just telling you the fucking truth.
‎我觉得这时候最好说明一下
This would be a good time to establish
‎伊舍威尔和总统都说过
that Isherwell and the president have both said
‎会有好处…
that there's benefits to be--
‎对 美国总统他妈的在说谎！
Right, well, the president of the United States is fucking lying!
‎我和你们一样
Look, I'm just like all of you.
‎天地良心 我希望 ‎这位总统知道自己在做什么
I hope to God, I hope to God that this president knows what she's doing.
‎我希望她能为我们考虑 但事实是
I hope she's got us all taken care of, but the truth is,
‎我觉得整届政府
I think this whole administration
‎都他妈完全疯了！
has completely lost their fucking mind!
‎我觉得我们都会死！
And I think we're all gonna die!
‎我只想回家
Look, I just wanna go home.
‎我现在除了回家什么都不想做
I just wanna go home. I just wanna go home more than anything.
‎但只有一件事
But if there is one thing,
‎有一件事我希望你们能听进去
one thing that I pray…that I pray that all of you hear from what I have just said,
‎那就是我们所有人 我们都…
is that all of us, all of us…
‎你为什么要这么做？
Why'd you do that?
‎我本来真的挺喜欢你的 ‎大部分人都让我厌恶
I really liked you and I despise most people.
‎我真的以为我爱你
You know, I… I really thought I loved you.
‎真的吗？
Really?
‎哇
Wow.
‎太疯狂了
That's wild.
‎是啊
-Yeah.
‎女士 你得离开了 ‎我们要让这个人与外界隔离
Ma'am, you need to go. We gotta get this man off the grid.
‎你还在吗？
You still there?
‎不在
No.
‎也许他就是在玩弄权力
Well, maybe he just gets off on the power, you know,
‎跟任何一种权力一样
like any kind of power.
‎他知道我最终会发现零食是免费的
It's like he knew eventually that I was gonna find out that the snacks were free.
‎对
-Right. You know what I mean?
‎-你明白吗？ ‎-嗯
-Yeah.
‎这就是玩弄权力
So it was just like a power play.
‎男人都很奇怪
Yeah, guys are weird.
‎我开始觉得 ‎这些“世界末日”的言论都是胡扯
I'm starting to think that all this "end of the world" stuff is bullshit.
‎不是的
It's not.
‎真的会发生 我看到了
It's definitely happening. I've seen it.
‎我不知道 ‎我觉得如果上帝想摧毁地球
I feel like if God wanted to destroy the Earth,
‎祂就会摧毁地球
He would destroy the Earth.
‎你相信上帝？
You believe in God?
‎是的 我父母按福音派教义把我养大
Yeah, I mean, my parents raised me Evangelical,
‎我恨他们 ‎但我以自己的方式接受了它
and I hate them, but I found my own way to it.
‎我自己的连接
My own relationship.
‎希望你不会说出去 我会感激你的
I'd appreciate it if you didn't advertise it, though.
‎我不会跟别人说的 我觉得这样挺好
I won't tell anybody. I think it's kind of sweet.
‎-要做爱吗？ ‎-好 干吗不做呢？
-Wanna make out? Yeah, why not?
‎能不能别说“干吗不做呢”？ ‎让我感觉你并不想做
Can you not say "why not"? It makes me feel like you don't want it.
‎很不舒服
It's shitty.
‎-好 随便吧 ‎-好多了
-Sure, whatever. That's better.
♪ I still feel 25 Most of the time ♪
♪ I still raise a little Cain With the boys ♪
♪ Honky tonks and pretty… ♪
‎-哦 我的天 就是它 ‎-什么？
-Oh, my God, that's it. What? What?
‎-那就是彗星 ‎-什么？在哪儿？
-That's the comet. What? Where?
‎-哪儿？ ‎-那是北斗七星
Where? Uh-huh. Well, that's the Big Dipper.
‎那是金星 那是北极星
-That's Venus. That's the North Star. Uh-huh.
‎-那是什么？ ‎-哦 该死
-Well, what is that? Oh, shit.
♪ Sometimes I feel like Jesse James Still trying to make a name ♪
‎搞什么？
What the hell? ♪ Knowing nothing's gonna change What I am ♪
‎什么？
What?
Come on.
‎它来了
There it is.
‎你来了
There you are.
‎有其他人看到吗？就是它
Is anyone else seeing this? That's it.
‎就是它 那就是彗星 看！就在那儿
That's it. That's the comet. Look! It's right there.
‎-我…我有点害怕 ‎-没错
-That's, you know, kinda scary. Oh! Exactly.
‎-明迪博士 ‎-凯特
-Dr. Mindy. Kate.
‎博士 可以看见它了
Doc, you can see it.
‎我现在也正看着它 难以置信 它…
I… I'm looking at it right now too. It's unbelievable. It's…
‎很可怕 但也很美
It's horrific and it's… And it's beautiful at the same time.
‎哦 我的天
-Oh, my God.
‎我们一直想告诉你们
We've been trying to tell you.
‎我们一直想告诉你们 ‎它就在那儿 它…
We tried to tell you this whole time. It's right there. It's…
‎就在那儿 凯特
It's right there, Kate.
‎你在哪儿？
Where are you?
‎我在密歇根的兰辛
I'm in Lansing, Michigan
‎想要修复和琼的关系 ‎但她不愿和我说话
trying to fix things with June, but she won't talk to me.
‎-你在哪儿？ ‎-什么东西？
-Where are you? What the fuck?
‎我…
I…
‎我去找你 好吗？
I'm gonna come find you, okay?
‎我在伊利诺伊 明天就能做好准备
Well, I'm in Illinois. I could be ready by tomorrow.
‎-挚爱的天父… ‎-是的 我…
-Dearest Father… Yeah, I'm--
‎…这个罪人 请求您的恩典和指引
…as a sinner I come to You for Your grace and guidance…
‎他们终于看到了
They're finally seeing it.
‎就在那里！
There it is!
‎到院子里去 上屋顶 去路边
Go outside into your yard, onto a roof, onto your sidewalk,
‎抬头看天空
and just look up into the sky.
‎这颗星看起来有点模糊
The star's gonna appear fuzzy.
‎但它后面有一条长尾巴
It's got a long streak coming off of it.
‎那是彗星尾
That's the comet's tail.
‎是真的 它来了
It's real and it's coming.
‎如果有人有不一样的说法 ‎那就是在胡扯
If anyone tells you any different, they're full of shit.
‎抬头看天空
Just look up into the sky.
‎他妈的真相
It's a fucking fact.
‎-我们有证据 ‎-快抬头
-We have proof. Just look up.
‎各位 快抬头 好吗？ ‎别管海牛了 快抬头
Guys, please just look up, okay? Screw the manatees and just look up.
‎快抬头
Just look up.
‎-快抬头！ ‎-快抬头！
Just look up! Just look up! Just look up!
‎快抬头！
Just look up!
‎明迪博士 总统拯救地球的计划
Dr. Mindy, the president's plan to save Earth
‎保卫所有人的家园 这会奏效的吧？
and make it so we can all have a home is going to work, right?
‎这个星球上 ‎每个男人、女人和小孩都会死
Every single man, woman and child on this planet is going to die.
‎-我不喜欢他 他让我难过 ‎-抱歉
-I don't like him. He makes me sad. I'm sorry about that.
‎-彩排不是这样说的 ‎-孩子们 听我说
-This is not what we rehearsed. Kids, listen.
‎告诉你们的家长 ‎奥尔林总统和伊舍威尔
You tell your parents that President Orlean and Isherwell
‎是反社会的法西斯主义者！
are sociopaths and fascists!
‎知道为什么他们希望你们抬头看吗？
And do you know why they want you to look up?
‎知道为什么吗？
Do you know why?
‎因为他们希望你们恐惧
'Cause they want you to be afraid.
‎他们希望你们抬头看
They want you to look up
‎因为他们正俯视着你们
because they are looking down their noses at you.
‎他们觉得自己比你们更优越
They think they're better than you.
‎孩子们 千万别抬头！
Don't look up!
‎他们想抢走你们的自由 这是事实！
They wanna rob you of your freedom, and that's a fact!
‎千万别抬头！
Don't look up!
‎美国总统奥尔林…
The US president, Orlean…
‎快抬头！
Just look up!
‎…没有让印度或世界上任何其他国家
…has not included India or any other nation in the world
‎参与这个任务
to be a part of this mission.
‎这家伙是个色情片发行人 ‎叫基普施莱辛格
This dude is a known pornographer named Kip…
‎别听那个傻子的
Don't listen to that dumbfuck.
‎联合国在考虑自己的偏航任务
The United Nations have been considering its own deflective mission.
‎快抬头 老天爷！
Just look up, for fuck's sake!
‎我知道好莱坞很多人支持快抬头运动
Now I know a lot of Hollywood is supporting the Just Look Up movement,
‎但我没看到那样的支持徽章
but I haven't seen a pin like that.
‎（德文彼得斯 《全面毁灭》）
Yeah, this pin points both up and down.
‎是的 这个徽章 ‎同时指了上下两个方向
‎因为我觉得 同在一个国家 ‎我们应该停止争吵
Because I think, as a country, we need to stop arguing
‎释放美德信号 好好相处
and virtue signaling. Just get along.
‎真是崭新的观点
That is so refreshing. Hmm.
‎我觉得我们都受够了政治
I think we're all tired of the politics.
‎是的…
Yeah, yeah. Well…
‎所以我们才拍了《全面毁灭》
That's why we made Total Devastation.
‎适合所有人观看 爆米花电影
It's for everyone. You know? It's a popcorn movie.
‎专注看好脚下的路 低下头
You keep your eye on the road ahead, you put your head down.
‎一步一个脚印
And you put one foot in front of the other,
‎向前走
step by step.
‎一天一天往前走
Day by day.
‎-别抬头！ ‎-别抬头！
Don't look up! Don't!
‎（《上》-立刻购买）
‎（已购买）
‎（直播 直播有延迟）
‎（真的最后一场救世演唱会）
‎我们想大声说清楚一些事情
So we wanna say something loud and clear.
‎没有安全的方法可以让彗星落入地球
There is no safe way to bring this comet back to Earth
‎并开发它来赚钱 这是不可能的！
and exploit it for profit. It cannot be done!
‎全球各个国家 反抗奥尔林和巴什
Nations of the world, defy Orlean and BASH!
‎马上发起你们自己的核弹偏航任务
Launch your own nuclear deflection mission now
‎拯救地球！
and save this planet!
‎现在要上场的是 ‎莱丽比纳和她的特别嘉宾
And now, uh, there's Riley Bina with her special guest.
‎我忘了他叫什么 谢谢
I forgot the name. Thank you.
‎（你真火辣！我们爱你 莱丽！）
‎（出五千美元换一把铲子 ‎彗星真会让我们都液化吗？）
‎（千万别抬头 ‎马克思贱人！莱丽是英雄）
‎（在彗星杀死我前看莱丽！ ‎我女朋友唱得比她好）
‎（我一个人在家 ‎饥渴难耐 只要3块99）
‎我们知道 没有界限可以和音速相比
♪ We knew no bounds Fell at the speed of sound ♪
‎突破万难而来 ‎但界限很快让我们有了隔阂
♪ Riding against all odds but soon Against ourselves ♪
‎你存在于每段记忆
♪ You haunted every memory ♪
‎未曾与我道别
♪ With no goodbyes out there for me ♪
‎你的骄傲熄灭了我们的火焰
♪ Your pride put out the fire In our flame ♪
‎只需看一眼
♪ Then just one look is all it takes ♪
‎我能感受到你的目光 ‎锁定在我全身每个地方
♪ I feel your eyes They're locked on every part of me ♪
‎然后我愚蠢的内心说
♪ And then my dumb heart says ♪
‎快抬头
♪ Just look up ♪
‎无处可藏
♪ There is no place to hide ♪
‎真爱不灭
♪ True love doesn't die ♪
‎抱紧你 绝不放开…
♪ It holds on tight And never lets you go… ♪
‎总统刚上演了 ‎一场满分十分的魅力秀吗？
Is that a rock-solid ten smokeshow of a president or what?
‎要不是她是我妈…
If she wasn't my mother…
‎有三类美国人
There's three types of American people.
‎你们工薪阶层
There are you, the working class.
‎我们酷炫的富人 还有他们
Us, the cool rich, and then them.
‎抱歉 但我们需要他们
I'm sorry, but we need them.
‎我们需要他们 是因为你们 ‎让我们变得强大 来对抗他们
We need them because you build us up to fight them.
‎工薪阶层 低等人
The working class, the lower.
‎-懂吗？ ‎-不 我不懂
-You understand? No, I don't get it.
‎懂吗？我说的是营养学家
Do you understand? I'm talking about… I'm talking about nutritionists.
‎我说的是私人教练
I'm talking about personal trainers,
‎水疗馆的人
people at the spa,
‎但不是给你办理登记的人 ‎她们不是女按摩师
but not the ones that check you in and they're not the masseuses,
‎但她们陪你走过走廊
but they walk you down the corridor.
‎她们在…
They're there…
‎我知道让你失望了 我无法否认
♪ Know I let you down A nigga can't deny it ♪
‎我们失去了很多 对 我很在乎
♪ And there's so much that we're losin' Yes, that matters ♪
‎我在应付自己的疯狂 ‎我不是你需要的人
♪ I've been dealin' with madness Wasn't the man you needed ♪
‎你在面对悲伤 真的 都怪我…
♪ You dealin' with sadness Truthfully, it's all on me… ♪
‎-什么时候抛弃巴什？ ‎-马上抛弃！
Divest from BASH when? Divest now!
‎什么时候抛弃巴什？
Divest from BASH when?
‎时间如此宝贵…
♪ Time is oh so precious… ♪
‎我们不会沉默！
We will not be quiet!
‎牵我的手 宝贝 ‎我不会再离开你 莱丽
♪ Take my hand, baby I'll never leave you, Riley ♪
‎女孩 他真正想说的是
♪ Though what he's really trying to say ♪
‎别再埋住你的脑袋
♪ Is get your head out of your ass ♪
‎听听合格的科学家的话
♪ Listen to the goddamn Qualified scientists ♪
‎我这次真的搞砸了 真的搞砸了
♪ We really fucked it up Fucked it up this time ♪
‎彗星好近 我能感受到强烈的热量
♪ It's so close I can feel the heat big-time ♪
‎你可以装作一切如常
♪ And you can act Like everything is all right ♪
‎但可能这真的在发生
♪ But this is probably Happening in real time ♪
‎庆祝吧 哭泣吧 祈祷吧
♪ Celebrate or cry or pray ♪
‎随便你如何度过我们搞砸的世界
♪ Whatever it takes To get you through the mess that we made ♪
‎因为明天也许不会来临
♪ 'Cause tomorrow may never come ♪
‎快抬头
♪ Just look up ♪
‎关掉垃圾新闻
♪ Turn off the shitbox news ♪
‎因为你就要死了 各位
♪ 'Cause you're about to die soon Everybody ♪
‎抬头…
♪ Look up… ♪
‎嘿 下午好 亚当 找我什么事？
Hey, good afternoon, Adam. What do I owe the pleasure of this call?
‎什么时间？
What time?
‎谢谢你打电话告诉我
Well, uh… Well, thank you for calling.
‎好
Yeah.
‎怎么了？
What?
‎奥尔林和巴什 ‎剥夺了俄罗斯、印度和中国
Orlean and BASH cut Russia, India, and China
‎对矿产的开采权
out of the rights for the minerals.
‎所以他们自行联合开展了偏航任务
So they tried their own joint deflection mission,
‎但是…大约40分钟前
but, uh… approximately 40 minutes ago,
‎俄罗斯拜科努尔发射中心 ‎检测到大规模爆炸
there was a massive explosion detected at the Russian's Baikonur launch complex.
‎看来任务失败了
So it looks like the mission failed.
‎就这样？
That's it?
‎“就这样”是什么意思？
What do you mean, "that's it? "
‎泰迪？
Teddy?
‎是吗？
Right?
‎还有巴什的任务 我们只剩这个了
There is still the BASH mission. It's all we have now.
‎妈的！
Fuck!
‎这些快抬头运动狂热者
These Just Look Uppers
‎想让上百万非法智利移民越过边境
want millions of illegal Chileans to come across the border.
‎千万别抬头
Don't look up.
‎（奥尔林）
‎（开采彗星）
‎那是什么玩意？
The hell is that?
‎你他妈骗我们
Fucking lied to us.
‎总统刚给我发了短信 ‎“别嗑药 没问题”
-The president just texted me. "Don't trip. It's all good. Don't trip. "
‎（千万别抬头）
‎嘿
Hey, now.
‎你们割伤我的脸了 乡下人！
You cut my face, you fucking rednecks!
‎天啊 开了一个小时都没看到车
Man, there hasn't been a car in, like, an hour.
‎是啊 大家都去看巴什发射了
Yep. Everyone's watching the BASH launch.
‎我们要干什么来着？
What are we doing again?
‎我说了 我们去采购些食品
I told you. We're, uh… We're gonna go buy some groceries.
‎米尔斯兄弟 ‎很棒的乐队 艾灵顿公爵创立的
The Mills Brothers. Great band. You know, Duke Ellington found this band.
‎我记得他们本来叫和谐四王
I think they were originally called the Four Kings of Harmony.
♪ We'll call on each memory Till then… ♪
‎这首歌是《到那时》
"Till Then, " this is the song. It's about, uh…
‎讲的是即将出征二战的士兵们
It's about soldiers going off to World War II
‎思念家乡
and thinking about home.
‎听这部分
Listen to this part. ♪ Although there are oceans… ♪
‎“尽管有必须跨越的海洋 ‎和必须翻越的山
"Although there are oceans we must cross and mountains that we must climb…"
♪ I know every gain… ♪
‎我知道有得必有失”
"I know that every gain must have a loss. "
‎“那就祈祷我们失去的只是时间”
♪ So pray that our loss… ♪ "So pray that our loss is nothing but time. "
♪ Till then, let's dream Of what there will be ♪
‎-我要问你一件事 ‎-怎么了？
Okay, I gotta ask you something. What?
‎明迪博士 我可以在你的车里 ‎表现得脆弱吗？
Dr. Mindy, can I be vulnerable in your car?
‎可以
Yeah, go ahead.
‎我见过很多人 但没见过你这样的
I've never met anyone like you
‎我觉得和你有共鸣
and I feel a connection to you on a level that…
‎我不知道 ‎没有别人让我有过这种感觉
I don't know, I haven't felt with anyone else,
‎我要冒险问一句
and going out on a limb,
‎你希望多共处一些时间吗？
but would you want to spend more time together?
‎也许甚至订婚什么的？
Maybe even get engaged or something?
‎-哇 ‎-你在笑吗？
-Wow. Are you laughing?
‎-没有？ ‎-我在微笑
-No? I'm smiling.
‎-当然可以 ‎-真好
-Well, sure. This is sweet.
‎-有何不可呢？ ‎-太美好了
-Why not? This is pretty sweet.
‎而你…你帮明迪博士解读了未来
And you read the tea leaves for Dr. Mindy.
‎-让他见识了算法 ‎-是的
-You showed him the algorithm. Oh, yeah.
‎你的信息真的吓到他了
You really shook him with that information.
‎-关于他的死法 ‎-是啊 让人震惊
-How he was gonna die. Yeah, it is shaking.
‎我好希望知道自己的死法
It got me so excited to know about my own death.
‎我还是不要知道了 不 我想知道
I don't think I wanna know. Yes, I do. I wanna to know.
‎你会被一头布朗特洛吃掉 ‎我们不知道这是什么意思
You're gonna be eaten by a Bronteroc. We don't know what it means.
‎-一头什么？ ‎-布朗特洛
-A what? A Bronteroc.
‎好了 各位 天气晴朗
-Oh. Okay, people, we have clear skies.
‎可以发射必得机了
And we are a go for the BEAD launch.
‎总统女士？
Madam President?
‎地球公民们 现在…
Citizens of planet Earth. Now…
‎看啊 凯特 他们有野生三文鱼
Look at this, Kate. They have wild salmon.
‎看看野生和养殖的区别
Look at the difference between that and the farm-raised stuff.
‎看起来…挺假的 是不是？
You see how that looks just… I don't know. Looks fake, right?
‎嘿 不如你去找点…
Hey, why don't you go find some, uh…
‎那种小土豆叫什么来着？
What are the little potatoes called, the tiny ones?
‎-吮指土豆？ ‎-对
-Fingerling potatoes? Yeah.
‎-我好爱吮指土豆 ‎-我们去找吮指…
-I fucking love fingerling potatoes. Let's get finger…
‎你想说点什么吗？
Do you wanna say something too?
‎说得太好了 好
That was beautiful. Yeah.
‎你们好吗 全世界的人们？ ‎我是美国白宫幕僚长 杰森奥尔林
What up, world? Jason Orlean, uh, Chief of Staff, United States.
‎我注意到近期很多人为人类祈祷
I've been noticing a lot of prayers recently for people during this time
‎我表示赞许
and I commend that, um,
‎但我也想为物品祈祷
but I also wanna give a prayer for stuff.
‎有很好的物品 物质类的东西 ‎比如豪华公寓和手表…
There's dope stuff, like material stuff, like sick apartments and watches,
‎（必得机已准备好发射）
‎…还有汽车和衣服之类的 ‎都有可能消失
and cars, um, and clothes and shit that could all go away and
‎我不想看到这些东西消失
I don't wanna see that stuff go away.
‎所以我要为这些物品祈祷 阿门
So I'm gonna say a prayer for that stuff. Amen.
‎在这个小了很多的人群中 ‎人们在恐惧中表现得很安静
Just a quiet trepidation among this much smaller crowd.
‎我能听到一些人的祈祷声
I can hear the sounds of some people praying.
‎好了 安德森 我们开始吧
Okay, Anderson, let's go get it.
‎好的 长官 来吧 各位 十
Yes, sir. Here we go, people.
‎十、九、八、七、六
Ten. Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
‎五、四…
five, four…
‎嘿
Hey.
‎嗨
Hi.
‎我们买了点东西
We, uh, got some groceries.
‎那是怎么回事？
Yo, what was that?
‎必得机12号坠毁了
-We lost BEAD number 12.
‎（警告）
‎必得机22号发射失败
BEAD number 22 failed to launch.
‎没事
It's fine. It's fine.
‎（必得机 无人机遥感勘测）
‎我们预估了容错误差 没事的
We had anticipated a margin for error.
‎我希望能有一次家庭晚餐
Everything is fine. I was hoping we could, um, have a family dinner.
‎-嘿 爸爸 ‎-嘿 爸爸
Hey, Dad.
‎-嘿 孩子们 ‎-嘿
-Hey, guys. Hey. Hey.
‎你觉得呢？
What do you say?
‎好吧
Yeah.
‎-谢谢 ‎-没事
Thank you. Yeah.
‎-这位是凯特 ‎-你好
-This is, uh… This is Kate. Oh, hi.
‎-你好 凯特 ‎-袋子给我
-Hello. Hi, Kate. Let me grab those bags.
‎-很高兴认识你 我叫尤尔 ‎-尤尔
-Nice to meet you. I'm Yule. Yule.
‎我的推趣账号是火豹142 ‎你打游戏吗？
I'm FirePuma142 on Twitch. You game?
‎她真的不太可能知道
It's really doubtful she knows.
‎谁说我打游戏的？
-You're right. Who said I game?
‎这是送给你的
I… I got these for you.
‎谢谢 真贴心 亲爱的
Thank you. That's really sweet, honey.
‎你不知道我有多歉疚
I'm so sorry. You have no idea.
‎-真的 ‎-我知道
-I really am. I know. I know.
‎-我想你 ‎-我非常想你
-I've missed you. I missed you so much.
‎我们在大学恋爱的时候 ‎我和阿伦特兰上过床
When we dated in college, I fucked Aaron Tran.
‎所以…
Oh? Yeah, so, uh…
‎尝尝
‎尝一个试试
‎很好吃
-That is really good.
‎好吃吧？
Really good, right?
‎-嘿 各位 ‎-嘿！
-Hey, everybody. Hey!
‎抱歉迟到了 但我没空手来
-Sorry I'm late, but not empty-handed. Hey, my friend.
‎埃文 马歇尔 琼 ‎这是奥格尔索普博士
Evan, Marshall, June, this is Dr. Oglethorpe.
‎必得机已达到最佳逃逸速度
BEADs have approached optimal escape velocity
‎现正靠近迪比亚斯基彗星 ‎准备进入接触模式
and now approaching Comet Dibiasky and are ready for attachment mode.
‎好吧
Uh… Okay. All right.
‎8号和27号因后控失灵坠毁
Eight and 27 are lost due to lateral control malfunction.
‎好 现在 彼得…
Okay, so, now… Now, Peter…
‎彼得 我们失去了 ‎六架无人机 还能成功吗？
Peter, we're six drones down. Is this thing still gonna work?
‎工程师向我保证可以 24架就够了
Well, the engineer's assured me that yes, 24 drones is enough.
‎我们还能失去几架？
Well, how many can we lose?
‎还有几架？
How many more?
‎我们得知 数架必得机在发射中爆炸
We're being told that several of the BEADS have exploded on launch.
‎你去坐主位吧 好吗？
-Got the head seat right there.
‎你太客气了 兰德尔 谢谢
You're way too kind, Randall. Thank you.
‎大博士
Big Doctor.
‎再来点酒吗？我给你倒
Do you want more wine?
‎-嘿 大家干杯 ‎-干杯
-Hey, cheers, everyone. Huh? Cheers.
‎-干杯 ‎-爱你 宝贝
-Cheers. Love you.
‎-爱你 ‎-非常感谢邀请我们
-Love you. Thank you so much for having us.
‎谢谢你们来 这是一次很特别的聚餐
Thank you for being here.
‎谢谢
-It's so special. Thank you.
‎马上开始同步爆破分离第九阶段
Commence simultaneous explosive separation stage now.
‎妈妈
Yo. Yo. Mom.
‎真好
Beautiful.
‎-谢谢你 伙计 ‎-是的
Thank you, pal. Yeah.
‎真的 你能回家真是太好了
Yeah, it really is. And it's really good to have you home.
‎明迪博士真的出名了
Dr. Mindy got really famous.
‎是啊 我都忘了 没错 好吧
Oh. Oh, yeah, I forgot about that. That's right. Okay.
‎是 我上过杂志封面什么的 我知道
Yep, I was on, uh, magazine covers and everything. I know.
‎-你看起来很棒 ‎-尽管嘲讽我吧
You looked great. I'll take your shots.
‎-我爱你 ‎-我也爱你
I love you. Love you too.
‎（系统故障）
‎好了 我们需要报告
All right. We need a report.
‎我需要爆炸设备的完整状态报告
Need a full status report on the explosive devices.
‎开始吧 还在等待完整状态报告
Get on it. Still waiting for a full status report.
‎好
All right.
‎中国的齐主席说彗星仍然是完整的
President Qi of China says that the comet is still whole.
‎我们有四架点火失败 同步已失灵
We got four misfires and sync was off.
‎彗星还是完好无损
It's still intact.
‎你说什么？
What was that?
‎我们有四架点火失败 同步已失灵
We've got four misfires and the sync was off.
‎好吧 没关系 大家都会没事的
Okay. We're all fine. Everyone's fine.
‎会没事的 失陪一下
It's gonna be all right. If you'll excuse me.
‎人有三急
Nature calls.
‎我去一下洗手间
I'm just gonna go to the restroom for a moment.
‎对 我想我也要去一下洗手间
Yes, uh, I think that I should also step out to the restroom for a moment.
‎-我是不是… ‎-不 我没事的
Should I… No, I'll be fine.
‎先生 总统
Sir, the president.
‎我们需要知道任务的状态
We need to know what the mission status is.
‎她马上会回来的
She's coming right back.
‎管他呢 我要去见我丈夫
Screw this. I'm going to see my husband.
‎抱歉 我有个20岁的女儿
I'm sorry. I've got a 20-year-old daughter.
‎我要去见她
I've got to go see her.
‎我要嗑药
I'm doin' an 8-ball.
‎哦 该死！
Oh, shit!
‎她马上就来
She's coming. She's coming back.
‎喂 有一艘飞船
Hello, there's a ship.
‎以防我们搞砸了 显然我们搞砸了
In case we were wrong, and clearly, we were wrong.
‎你们当然会有飞船
Of course you've got a ship.
‎可以装2000人
It holds 2, 000.
‎有最先进的冷冻仓 准备出发寻找
It's state-of-the-art cryo-chambers, and it's set to find
‎宜居地带最近的类地行星…
the nearest Earth-like planet in a Goldilocks Zone so…
‎你可以带一个人上来 ‎布里 你妻子 你自己选
Hmm. There's room for you and one other. Brie, your wife, your call.
‎我不用了 但谢谢你的邀请 ‎和杰森玩得开心
I'm good, but thank you for the offer. You, uh… You have fun with Jason.
‎杰森？
Jason?
‎哦 该死
Oh, shit.
‎她会回来的
She's coming back.
‎我感激的是在后院睡着的那个夜晚
I'm thankful for that night I fell asleep out in the backyard.
‎-我醒来时和一只小鹿面面相觑 ‎-我记得
-Woke up face-to-face with a baby deer. I remember that.
‎-是啊 ‎-对 那是我人生中最棒的一天
-Yeah. Yep. It was the best day of my life.
‎我感激的是…
I'm grateful…
‎我感激的是我们努力过了
I'm grateful we tried.
‎天啊 我们真的努力了
Man, oh, man, did we try.
‎我们明迪家不算最有宗教氛围的
Well, we're not the most religious here in the Mindy household,
‎但也许我们应该说“阿门”？ ‎是应该这么说吗？
but, um, maybe we should say "amen"? Should we do that?
‎别看我
Don't look at me.
‎我不知道怎么… ‎你刚说“阿门”？我不…
I don't know how to… What, you just say, "Amen"? I don't…
‎-交给我吧 ‎-收尾？
-I got this. Wrap it up?
‎我来
I got it.
‎挚爱的天父 全能的造物主
Dearest Father and Almighty Creator…
‎我们请求您的恩典 褪去我们的骄傲
…we ask for Your grace tonight, despite our pride.
‎您的谅解 消除我们的疑虑
Your forgiveness, despite our doubt.
‎最重要的是 主啊
Most of all, Lord…
‎我们请求您的爱 ‎抚慰我们度过至暗时刻
we ask for Your love to soothe us through these dark times.
‎愿我们无论面对什么…
May we face whatever is to come…
‎在您的神圣中 ‎我们将拥有勇气和接受的开阔胸襟
…in Your divine will with courage and open hearts of acceptance.
‎-阿门 ‎-阿门
-Amen. Amen.
‎哇 尤尔的教堂游戏玩得很溜啊
Wow. Youse got some church game.
‎真美好
That was beautiful.
‎彗星依然完整
The comet remains intact.
‎（突发新闻 ‎彗星完整：巴什任务失败）
‎我们从未…
We just never…
‎今晚所有人当然都只讨论一件事情
Of course, there's only one story everyone's talking about tonight.
‎脱衣紧急关怀中心…
Topless urgent care centers.
‎坐吧
Sit.
‎或者…我们可以做爱
Or… we can fuck…
‎或者祈祷 或者…
…or pray, or…
‎说实话 我宁愿喝酒…
Honestly, I think I'd just rather drink and…
‎说说别人的坏话
talk shit about people.
‎你别想活捉我！
You'll never take me alive!
‎小心！
Look out!
‎我肯定要再吃一块苹果派 太香了
I'm definitely gonna have some more of this apple pie. It's so good.
‎其实是超市买的 但根本吃不出来
It's actually store-bought, but you really can't tell.
‎我得说句实话 ‎这种时候有何不可呢？
If I'm to be completely honest, which at this moment, why not?
‎比起家里做的 ‎我更喜欢超市买来的廉价口感
I actually like the junky taste of store-bought better than homemade.
‎你开玩笑的吧
You gotta be kidding me.
‎不 我没开玩笑
No, I'm not kidding.
‎我懂他的意思 算是一种童年记忆
You know what? I know what he means. It's like a childhood memory thing.
‎没有什么比得上家里做的吧？
Nothing is better than homemade, right?
‎这咖啡的味道不像超市买的吧？
This coffee doesn't taste store-bought. Is it?
‎我自己磨豆子 是的
I grind my own beans. Yeah.
‎是 爸爸是个咖啡爱好者
Yeah, Dad's kind of a coffee nut.
‎每次喝咖啡都要自己磨豆子？
Every time you have coffee, you have to grind your beans?
‎兰德尔对咖啡要求很高
Randall is very particular about his coffee.
‎我喝茶也是这样
I can get that way about tea.
‎事实是 我们真的…
Thing of it is, we really…
‎我们真的该有的都有了 是不是？
We really did have everything, didn't we?
‎仔细想想
I mean, when you think about it.
♪ Is this our first? ♪
♪ Or second nature? ♪
‎（恭喜！减肥结束！）
♪ When's that Rapture?  ♪
♪ Will there be merch? ♪
♪ Where is Mother? She was a stunner ♪
♪ Can we page her? ♪
♪ What mine eyes have seen Could really take the purse ♪
♪ Are we chumps now?  ♪
♪ Or are we fakers? ♪
♪ Parade around or get in work? ♪
♪ Or just deserve? ♪
♪ We will see you next time ♪
♪ There'll be water in the rain ♪
♪ Territories pay fines ♪
♪ All long day ♪
♪ All may not be just fine ♪
♪ There is another fate, a way ♪
♪ To not be too late ♪
♪ All obfuscate ♪
‎（22740年后）
‎（国际银行-吉尔阿诺德）
‎（德仕康石油-泰德拜尔斯）
‎（文德尔游说-路易斯格兰迪）
‎嘿 含氧量实际要高于地球
Hey, oxygen is actually higher than on Earth
‎高9%
by nine percent,
‎所以可能会觉得有点头晕
so you might feel a bit light-headed.
‎冷冻仓的成功率是58%
And cryo-chambers were 58% successful,
‎比预期好多了
which is much better than anticipated.
‎我们这个区只死了47个人 所以…
Yeah, we only had 47 dead in our section, so…
‎我觉得应该会挺顺利的 真的
I think this is gonna work out quite well. Quite well, indeed.
‎天啊
Goodness.
‎看看这只美丽的动物
Look at that beautiful animal.
‎这是羽毛还是鳞片…
I wonder, are those feathers or are they scale--
‎-好恶心 ‎-那是什么东西？
-That's disgusting. What is that thing?
‎我相信它是叫布朗特洛
I believe that's called a Bronteroc.
‎随便怎样都好 但别摸它们
Uh… Whatever you do, don't pet them.
♪ We will see you next time ♪
♪ There'll be water in the rain ♪
♪ Territories pay fines ♪
♪ All long day ♪
♪ All may not be just fine ♪
♪ There is another fate, a way ♪
♪ To not be too late ♪
♪ We will see you next time ♪
♪ There'll be water in the rain ♪
♪ Territories pay fines ♪
♪ All long day ♪
-♪ Say it with me ♪ ♪ All may not be just fine ♪
♪ There is another fate, a way ♪
♪ To not be too late ♪
♪ All obfuscate ♪
‎（纪念哈尔维尔纳
‎1956-2020）
‎该死
Fuck.
‎妈？
Mom?
‎妈！
Mom!
‎你们好吗？
What's up, y'all?
‎我是地球上最后一个人类
I'm the last man on Earth.
‎全完蛋了
Shit's all fucked up.
‎别忘了点赞加关注
Don't forget to like and subscribe.
‎走了
We out here.
‎妈！
Mom!
‎字幕翻译： 张珺怡